split,sentence_id,token_id,token,label
train,1,1,Sara,B-PERSON
train,1,2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
train,1,3,joined,O
train,1,4,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,1,5,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,1,6,in,O
train,1,7,Saudi,B-LOCATION
train,1,8,Arabia,I-LOCATION
train,1,9,on,O
train,1,10,March,B-DATE
train,1,11,2026,I-DATE
train,1,12,to,O
train,1,13,work,O
train,1,14,on,O
train,1,15,transformer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,1,16,architecture,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,1,17,.,O
train,2,1,Zainab,B-PERSON
train,2,2,Iqbal,I-PERSON
train,2,3,presented,O
train,2,4,a,O
train,2,5,project,O
train,2,6,on,O
train,2,7,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,2,8,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,2,9,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,2,10,at,O
train,2,11,Arbisoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,2,12,during,O
train,2,13,15,B-DATE
train,2,14,July,I-DATE
train,2,15,2026,I-DATE
train,2,16,.,O
train,3,1,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
train,3,2,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
train,3,3,announced,O
train,3,4,a,O
train,3,5,new,O
train,3,6,natural,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,3,7,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,3,8,processing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,3,9,team,O
train,3,10,in,O
train,3,11,Pakistan,B-LOCATION
train,3,12,on,O
train,3,13,next,B-DATE
train,3,14,Friday,I-DATE
train,3,15,.,O
train,4,1,Jamal,B-PERSON
train,4,2,Masood,I-PERSON
train,4,3,is,O
train,4,4,an,O
train,4,5,engineer,O
train,4,6,from,O
train,4,7,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,4,8,with,O
train,4,9,experience,O
train,4,10,in,O
train,4,11,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,4,12,.,O
train,5,1,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,5,2,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,5,3,is,O
train,5,4,hiring,O
train,5,5,graduates,O
train,5,6,skilled,O
train,5,7,in,O
train,5,8,semantic,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,5,9,search,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,5,10,for,O
train,5,11,its,O
train,5,12,Doha,B-LOCATION
train,5,13,office,O
train,5,14,.,O
train,6,1,Mehwish,B-PERSON
train,6,2,Akhtar,I-PERSON
train,6,3,will,O
train,6,4,attend,O
train,6,5,an,O
train,6,6,interview,O
train,6,7,at,O
train,6,8,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,6,9,on,O
train,6,10,December,B-DATE
train,6,11,2025,I-DATE
train,6,12,.,O
train,8,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
train,8,2,Noor,I-PERSON
train,8,3,used,O
train,8,4,BIO,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,8,5,tagging,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,8,6,to,O
train,8,7,improve,O
train,8,8,a,O
train,8,9,product,O
train,8,10,built,O
train,8,11,for,O
train,8,12,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,8,13,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,8,14,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,8,15,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,8,16,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,8,17,.,O
train,9,1,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,9,2,released,O
train,9,3,its,O
train,9,4,large,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,9,5,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,9,6,models,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,9,7,research,O
train,9,8,report,O
train,9,9,in,O
train,9,10,26,B-DATE
train,9,11,June,I-DATE
train,9,12,2026,I-DATE
train,9,13,.,O
train,10,1,Ali,B-PERSON
train,10,2,Raza,I-PERSON
train,10,3,moved,O
train,10,4,to,O
train,10,5,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,10,6,in,O
train,10,7,26,B-DATE
train,10,8,June,I-DATE
train,10,9,2026,I-DATE
train,10,10,and,O
train,10,11,started,O
train,10,12,learning,O
train,10,13,prompt,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,10,14,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,10,15,.,O
train,11,1,Mahnoor,B-PERSON
train,11,2,Rehman,I-PERSON
train,11,3,joined,O
train,11,4,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,11,5,in,O
train,11,6,Johar,B-LOCATION
train,11,7,Town,I-LOCATION
train,11,8,on,O
train,11,9,June,B-DATE
train,11,10,2026,I-DATE
train,11,11,to,O
train,11,12,work,O
train,11,13,on,O
train,11,14,multi,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,11,15,agent,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,11,16,systems,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,11,17,.,O
train,12,1,Omar,B-PERSON
train,12,2,Farooq,I-PERSON
train,12,3,presented,O
train,12,4,a,O
train,12,5,project,O
train,12,6,on,O
train,12,7,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,12,8,at,O
train,12,9,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,12,10,during,O
train,12,11,October,B-DATE
train,12,12,2026,I-DATE
train,12,13,.,O
train,13,1,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,13,2,announced,O
train,13,3,a,O
train,13,4,new,O
train,13,5,feature,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,13,6,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,13,7,team,O
train,13,8,in,O
train,13,9,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,13,10,on,O
train,13,11,April,B-DATE
train,13,12,2025,I-DATE
train,13,13,.,O
train,14,1,Mahnoor,B-PERSON
train,14,2,Rehman,I-PERSON
train,14,3,is,O
train,14,4,an,O
train,14,5,engineer,O
train,14,6,from,O
train,14,7,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
train,14,8,Lahore,I-LOCATION
train,14,9,with,O
train,14,10,experience,O
train,14,11,in,O
train,14,12,REST,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,14,13,API,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,14,14,.,O
train,15,1,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,15,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,15,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,15,4,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,15,5,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,15,6,is,O
train,15,7,hiring,O
train,15,8,graduates,O
train,15,9,skilled,O
train,15,10,in,O
train,15,11,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,15,12,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,15,13,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,15,14,for,O
train,15,15,its,O
train,15,16,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,15,17,office,O
train,15,18,.,O
train,17,1,The,O
train,17,2,feature,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,17,3,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,17,4,system,O
train,17,5,was,O
train,17,6,developed,O
train,17,7,by,O
train,17,8,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,17,9,in,O
train,17,10,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,17,11,.,O
train,18,1,Hira,B-PERSON
train,18,2,Shah,I-PERSON
train,18,3,used,O
train,18,4,retrieval,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,18,5,augmented,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,18,6,generation,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,18,7,to,O
train,18,8,improve,O
train,18,9,a,O
train,18,10,product,O
train,18,11,built,O
train,18,12,for,O
train,18,13,Arbisoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,18,14,.,O
train,19,1,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,19,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,19,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,19,4,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,19,5,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,19,6,released,O
train,19,7,its,O
train,19,8,feature,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,19,9,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,19,10,research,O
train,19,11,report,O
train,19,12,in,O
train,19,13,today,B-DATE
train,19,14,.,O
train,20,1,Ali,B-PERSON
train,20,2,Raza,I-PERSON
train,20,3,moved,O
train,20,4,to,O
train,20,5,United,B-LOCATION
train,20,6,Arab,I-LOCATION
train,20,7,Emirates,I-LOCATION
train,20,8,in,O
train,20,9,January,B-DATE
train,20,10,2025,I-DATE
train,20,11,and,O
train,20,12,started,O
train,20,13,learning,O
train,20,14,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,20,15,.,O
train,21,1,Zainab,B-PERSON
train,21,2,Iqbal,I-PERSON
train,21,3,joined,O
train,21,4,Arbisoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,21,5,in,O
train,21,6,Riyadh,B-LOCATION
train,21,7,on,O
train,21,8,next,B-DATE
train,21,9,Friday,I-DATE
train,21,10,to,O
train,21,11,work,O
train,21,12,on,O
train,21,13,BIO,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,21,14,tagging,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,21,15,.,O
train,22,1,Mehwish,B-PERSON
train,22,2,Akhtar,I-PERSON
train,22,3,presented,O
train,22,4,a,O
train,22,5,project,O
train,22,6,on,O
train,22,7,MLOps,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,22,8,at,O
train,22,9,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,22,10,during,O
train,22,11,26,B-DATE
train,22,12,June,I-DATE
train,22,13,2026,I-DATE
train,22,14,.,O
train,23,1,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,23,2,announced,O
train,23,3,a,O
train,23,4,new,O
train,23,5,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,23,6,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,23,7,team,O
train,23,8,in,O
train,23,9,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
train,23,10,Lahore,I-LOCATION
train,23,11,on,O
train,23,12,June,B-DATE
train,23,13,2026,I-DATE
train,23,14,.,O
train,24,1,Danish,B-PERSON
train,24,2,Ali,I-PERSON
train,24,3,is,O
train,24,4,an,O
train,24,5,engineer,O
train,24,6,from,O
train,24,7,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,24,8,with,O
train,24,9,experience,O
train,24,10,in,O
train,24,11,REST,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,24,12,API,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,24,13,.,O
train,25,1,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,25,2,is,O
train,25,3,hiring,O
train,25,4,graduates,O
train,25,5,skilled,O
train,25,6,in,O
train,25,7,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,25,8,for,O
train,25,9,its,O
train,25,10,United,B-LOCATION
train,25,11,Arab,I-LOCATION
train,25,12,Emirates,I-LOCATION
train,25,13,office,O
train,25,14,.,O
train,26,1,Omar,B-PERSON
train,26,2,Farooq,I-PERSON
train,26,3,will,O
train,26,4,attend,O
train,26,5,an,O
train,26,6,interview,O
train,26,7,at,O
train,26,8,Arbisoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,26,9,on,O
train,26,10,January,B-DATE
train,26,11,2025,I-DATE
train,26,12,.,O
train,27,1,The,O
train,27,2,REST,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,27,3,API,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,27,4,system,O
train,27,5,was,O
train,27,6,developed,O
train,27,7,by,O
train,27,8,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,27,9,in,O
train,27,10,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,27,11,.,O
train,28,1,Sana,B-PERSON
train,28,2,Javed,I-PERSON
train,28,3,used,O
train,28,4,prompt,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,28,5,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,28,6,to,O
train,28,7,improve,O
train,28,8,a,O
train,28,9,product,O
train,28,10,built,O
train,28,11,for,O
train,28,12,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
train,28,13,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
train,28,14,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
train,28,15,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
train,28,16,.,O
train,29,1,Arbisoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,29,2,released,O
train,29,3,its,O
train,29,4,named,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,29,5,entity,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,29,6,recognition,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,29,7,research,O
train,29,8,report,O
train,29,9,in,O
train,29,10,December,B-DATE
train,29,11,2025,I-DATE
train,29,12,.,O
train,30,1,Ayesha,B-PERSON
train,30,2,Khan,I-PERSON
train,30,3,moved,O
train,30,4,to,O
train,30,5,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,30,6,in,O
train,30,7,January,B-DATE
train,30,8,2025,I-DATE
train,30,9,and,O
train,30,10,started,O
train,30,11,learning,O
train,30,12,feature,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,30,13,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,30,14,.,O
train,31,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
train,31,2,Noor,I-PERSON
train,31,3,joined,O
train,31,4,National,B-ORGANIZATION
train,31,5,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,31,6,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,31,7,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,31,8,and,I-ORGANIZATION
train,31,9,Technology,I-ORGANIZATION
train,31,10,in,O
train,31,11,United,B-LOCATION
train,31,12,Arab,I-LOCATION
train,31,13,Emirates,I-LOCATION
train,31,14,on,O
train,31,15,next,B-DATE
train,31,16,Friday,I-DATE
train,31,17,to,O
train,31,18,work,O
train,31,19,on,O
train,31,20,data,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,31,21,preprocessing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,31,22,.,O
train,32,1,Ali,B-PERSON
train,32,2,Raza,I-PERSON
train,32,3,presented,O
train,32,4,a,O
train,32,5,project,O
train,32,6,on,O
train,32,7,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,32,8,at,O
train,32,9,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,32,10,during,O
train,32,11,September,B-DATE
train,32,12,2026,I-DATE
train,32,13,.,O
train,33,1,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,33,2,announced,O
train,33,3,a,O
train,33,4,new,O
train,33,5,machine,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,33,6,learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,33,7,team,O
train,33,8,in,O
train,33,9,Doha,B-LOCATION
train,33,10,on,O
train,33,11,April,B-DATE
train,33,12,2025,I-DATE
train,33,13,.,O
train,34,1,Sara,B-PERSON
train,34,2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
train,34,3,is,O
train,34,4,an,O
train,34,5,engineer,O
train,34,6,from,O
train,34,7,Silicon,B-LOCATION
train,34,8,Valley,I-LOCATION
train,34,9,with,O
train,34,10,experience,O
train,34,11,in,O
train,34,12,MLOps,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,34,13,.,O
train,35,1,National,B-ORGANIZATION
train,35,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,35,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,35,4,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,35,5,and,I-ORGANIZATION
train,35,6,Technology,I-ORGANIZATION
train,35,7,is,O
train,35,8,hiring,O
train,35,9,graduates,O
train,35,10,skilled,O
train,35,11,in,O
train,35,12,large,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,35,13,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,35,14,models,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,35,15,for,O
train,35,16,its,O
train,35,17,United,B-LOCATION
train,35,18,Arab,I-LOCATION
train,35,19,Emirates,I-LOCATION
train,35,20,office,O
train,35,21,.,O
train,36,1,Maryam,B-PERSON
train,36,2,Tariq,I-PERSON
train,36,3,will,O
train,36,4,attend,O
train,36,5,an,O
train,36,6,interview,O
train,36,7,at,O
train,36,8,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,36,9,on,O
train,36,10,December,B-DATE
train,36,11,2025,I-DATE
train,36,12,.,O
train,37,1,The,O
train,37,2,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,37,3,system,O
train,37,4,was,O
train,37,5,developed,O
train,37,6,by,O
train,37,7,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,37,8,in,O
train,37,9,Johar,B-LOCATION
train,37,10,Town,I-LOCATION
train,37,11,.,O
train,38,1,Sara,B-PERSON
train,38,2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
train,38,3,used,O
train,38,4,feature,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,38,5,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,38,6,to,O
train,38,7,improve,O
train,38,8,a,O
train,38,9,product,O
train,38,10,built,O
train,38,11,for,O
train,38,12,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
train,38,13,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
train,38,14,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
train,38,15,.,O
train,39,1,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,39,2,released,O
train,39,3,its,O
train,39,4,prompt,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,39,5,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,39,6,research,O
train,39,7,report,O
train,39,8,in,O
train,39,9,January,B-DATE
train,39,10,2025,I-DATE
train,39,11,.,O
train,40,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
train,40,2,Noor,I-PERSON
train,40,3,moved,O
train,40,4,to,O
train,40,5,Johar,B-LOCATION
train,40,6,Town,I-LOCATION
train,40,7,in,O
train,40,8,October,B-DATE
train,40,9,2026,I-DATE
train,40,10,and,O
train,40,11,started,O
train,40,12,learning,O
train,40,13,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,40,14,.,O
train,41,1,Jamal,B-PERSON
train,41,2,Masood,I-PERSON
train,41,3,joined,O
train,41,4,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,41,5,in,O
train,41,6,Dubai,B-LOCATION
train,41,7,on,O
train,41,8,December,B-DATE
train,41,9,2025,I-DATE
train,41,10,to,O
train,41,11,work,O
train,41,12,on,O
train,41,13,machine,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,41,14,learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,41,15,.,O
train,42,1,Sara,B-PERSON
train,42,2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
train,42,3,presented,O
train,42,4,a,O
train,42,5,project,O
train,42,6,on,O
train,42,7,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,42,8,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,42,9,at,O
train,42,10,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
train,42,11,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
train,42,12,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
train,42,13,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
train,42,14,during,O
train,42,15,October,B-DATE
train,42,16,2026,I-DATE
train,42,17,.,O
train,43,1,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,43,2,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,43,3,announced,O
train,43,4,a,O
train,43,5,new,O
train,43,6,REST,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,43,7,API,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,43,8,team,O
train,43,9,in,O
train,43,10,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,43,11,on,O
train,43,12,October,B-DATE
train,43,13,2026,I-DATE
train,43,14,.,O
train,44,1,Ali,B-PERSON
train,44,2,Raza,I-PERSON
train,44,3,is,O
train,44,4,an,O
train,44,5,engineer,O
train,44,6,from,O
train,44,7,Saudi,B-LOCATION
train,44,8,Arabia,I-LOCATION
train,44,9,with,O
train,44,10,experience,O
train,44,11,in,O
train,44,12,named,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,44,13,entity,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,44,14,recognition,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,44,15,.,O
train,45,1,National,B-ORGANIZATION
train,45,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,45,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,45,4,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,45,5,and,I-ORGANIZATION
train,45,6,Technology,I-ORGANIZATION
train,45,7,is,O
train,45,8,hiring,O
train,45,9,graduates,O
train,45,10,skilled,O
train,45,11,in,O
train,45,12,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,45,13,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,45,14,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,45,15,for,O
train,45,16,its,O
train,45,17,Islamabad,B-LOCATION
train,45,18,office,O
train,45,19,.,O
train,46,1,Nida,B-PERSON
train,46,2,Aslam,I-PERSON
train,46,3,will,O
train,46,4,attend,O
train,46,5,an,O
train,46,6,interview,O
train,46,7,at,O
train,46,8,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,46,9,on,O
train,46,10,March,B-DATE
train,46,11,2026,I-DATE
train,46,12,.,O
train,47,1,The,O
train,47,2,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,47,3,system,O
train,47,4,was,O
train,47,5,developed,O
train,47,6,by,O
train,47,7,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,47,8,in,O
train,47,9,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,47,10,.,O
train,48,1,Hamza,B-PERSON
train,48,2,Siddiqui,I-PERSON
train,48,3,used,O
train,48,4,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,48,5,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,48,6,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,48,7,to,O
train,48,8,improve,O
train,48,9,a,O
train,48,10,product,O
train,48,11,built,O
train,48,12,for,O
train,48,13,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,48,14,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,48,15,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,48,16,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,48,17,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,48,18,.,O
train,49,1,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,49,2,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
train,49,3,released,O
train,49,4,its,O
train,49,5,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,49,6,research,O
train,49,7,report,O
train,49,8,in,O
train,49,9,1,B-DATE
train,49,10,August,I-DATE
train,49,11,2026,I-DATE
train,49,12,.,O
train,50,1,Sara,B-PERSON
train,50,2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
train,50,3,moved,O
train,50,4,to,O
train,50,5,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,50,6,in,O
train,50,7,15,B-DATE
train,50,8,July,I-DATE
train,50,9,2026,I-DATE
train,50,10,and,O
train,50,11,started,O
train,50,12,learning,O
train,50,13,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,50,14,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,50,15,.,O
train,51,1,Jamal,B-PERSON
train,51,2,Masood,I-PERSON
train,51,3,joined,O
train,51,4,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,51,5,in,O
train,51,6,Doha,B-LOCATION
train,51,7,on,O
train,51,8,Monday,B-DATE
train,51,9,to,O
train,51,10,work,O
train,51,11,on,O
train,51,12,REST,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,51,13,API,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,51,14,.,O
train,52,1,Zainab,B-PERSON
train,52,2,Iqbal,I-PERSON
train,52,3,presented,O
train,52,4,a,O
train,52,5,project,O
train,52,6,on,O
train,52,7,feature,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,52,8,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,52,9,at,O
train,52,10,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,52,11,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,52,12,during,O
train,52,13,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,52,14,.,O
train,53,1,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,53,2,announced,O
train,53,3,a,O
train,53,4,new,O
train,53,5,natural,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,53,6,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,53,7,processing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,53,8,team,O
train,53,9,in,O
train,53,10,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,53,11,on,O
train,53,12,October,B-DATE
train,53,13,2026,I-DATE
train,53,14,.,O
train,54,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
train,54,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
train,54,3,is,O
train,54,4,an,O
train,54,5,engineer,O
train,54,6,from,O
train,54,7,Doha,B-LOCATION
train,54,8,with,O
train,54,9,experience,O
train,54,10,in,O
train,54,11,BIO,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,54,12,tagging,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,54,13,.,O
train,55,1,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,55,2,is,O
train,55,3,hiring,O
train,55,4,graduates,O
train,55,5,skilled,O
train,55,6,in,O
train,55,7,multi,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,55,8,agent,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,55,9,systems,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,55,10,for,O
train,55,11,its,O
train,55,12,Doha,B-LOCATION
train,55,13,office,O
train,55,14,.,O
train,56,1,Saad,B-PERSON
train,56,2,Qureshi,I-PERSON
train,56,3,will,O
train,56,4,attend,O
train,56,5,an,O
train,56,6,interview,O
train,56,7,at,O
train,56,8,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,56,9,on,O
train,56,10,Monday,B-DATE
train,56,11,.,O
train,57,1,The,O
train,57,2,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,57,3,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,57,4,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,57,5,system,O
train,57,6,was,O
train,57,7,developed,O
train,57,8,by,O
train,57,9,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,57,10,in,O
train,57,11,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,57,12,.,O
train,58,1,Sana,B-PERSON
train,58,2,Javed,I-PERSON
train,58,3,used,O
train,58,4,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,58,5,to,O
train,58,6,improve,O
train,58,7,a,O
train,58,8,product,O
train,58,9,built,O
train,58,10,for,O
train,58,11,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
train,58,12,.,O
train,59,1,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
train,59,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,59,3,released,O
train,59,4,its,O
train,59,5,large,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,59,6,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,59,7,models,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,59,8,research,O
train,59,9,report,O
train,59,10,in,O
train,59,11,today,B-DATE
train,59,12,.,O
train,60,1,Ayesha,B-PERSON
train,60,2,Khan,I-PERSON
train,60,3,moved,O
train,60,4,to,O
train,60,5,Saudi,B-LOCATION
train,60,6,Arabia,I-LOCATION
train,60,7,in,O
train,60,8,26,B-DATE
train,60,9,June,I-DATE
train,60,10,2026,I-DATE
train,60,11,and,O
train,60,12,started,O
train,60,13,learning,O
train,60,14,large,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,60,15,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,60,16,models,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,60,17,.,O
train,61,1,Zainab,B-PERSON
train,61,2,Iqbal,I-PERSON
train,61,3,joined,O
train,61,4,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,61,5,in,O
train,61,6,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,61,7,on,O
train,61,8,1,B-DATE
train,61,9,August,I-DATE
train,61,10,2026,I-DATE
train,61,11,to,O
train,61,12,work,O
train,61,13,on,O
train,61,14,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,61,15,.,O
train,62,1,Usman,B-PERSON
train,62,2,Malik,I-PERSON
train,62,3,presented,O
train,62,4,a,O
train,62,5,project,O
train,62,6,on,O
train,62,7,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,62,8,at,O
train,62,9,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,62,10,during,O
train,62,11,March,B-DATE
train,62,12,2026,I-DATE
train,62,13,.,O
train,63,1,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
train,63,2,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
train,63,3,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
train,63,4,announced,O
train,63,5,a,O
train,63,6,new,O
train,63,7,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,63,8,team,O
train,63,9,in,O
train,63,10,Silicon,B-LOCATION
train,63,11,Valley,I-LOCATION
train,63,12,on,O
train,63,13,15,B-DATE
train,63,14,July,I-DATE
train,63,15,2026,I-DATE
train,63,16,.,O
train,64,1,Mehwish,B-PERSON
train,64,2,Akhtar,I-PERSON
train,64,3,is,O
train,64,4,an,O
train,64,5,engineer,O
train,64,6,from,O
train,64,7,Lahore,B-LOCATION
train,64,8,with,O
train,64,9,experience,O
train,64,10,in,O
train,64,11,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,64,12,.,O
train,65,1,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
train,65,2,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
train,65,3,is,O
train,65,4,hiring,O
train,65,5,graduates,O
train,65,6,skilled,O
train,65,7,in,O
train,65,8,transformer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,65,9,architecture,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,65,10,for,O
train,65,11,its,O
train,65,12,Silicon,B-LOCATION
train,65,13,Valley,I-LOCATION
train,65,14,office,O
train,65,15,.,O
train,66,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
train,66,2,Noor,I-PERSON
train,66,3,will,O
train,66,4,attend,O
train,66,5,an,O
train,66,6,interview,O
train,66,7,at,O
train,66,8,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,66,9,on,O
train,66,10,December,B-DATE
train,66,11,2025,I-DATE
train,66,12,.,O
train,67,1,The,O
train,67,2,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,67,3,system,O
train,67,4,was,O
train,67,5,developed,O
train,67,6,by,O
train,67,7,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
train,67,8,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
train,67,9,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
train,67,10,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
train,67,11,in,O
train,67,12,Lahore,B-LOCATION
train,67,13,.,O
train,68,1,Jamal,B-PERSON
train,68,2,Masood,I-PERSON
train,68,3,used,O
train,68,4,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,68,5,to,O
train,68,6,improve,O
train,68,7,a,O
train,68,8,product,O
train,68,9,built,O
train,68,10,for,O
train,68,11,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,68,12,.,O
train,69,1,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,69,2,released,O
train,69,3,its,O
train,69,4,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,69,5,research,O
train,69,6,report,O
train,69,7,in,O
train,69,8,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,69,9,.,O
train,70,1,Nida,B-PERSON
train,70,2,Aslam,I-PERSON
train,70,3,moved,O
train,70,4,to,O
train,70,5,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,70,6,in,O
train,70,7,March,B-DATE
train,70,8,2026,I-DATE
train,70,9,and,O
train,70,10,started,O
train,70,11,learning,O
train,70,12,retrieval,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,70,13,augmented,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,70,14,generation,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,70,15,.,O
train,71,1,Ayesha,B-PERSON
train,71,2,Khan,I-PERSON
train,71,3,joined,O
train,71,4,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,71,5,in,O
train,71,6,Saudi,B-LOCATION
train,71,7,Arabia,I-LOCATION
train,71,8,on,O
train,71,9,1,B-DATE
train,71,10,August,I-DATE
train,71,11,2026,I-DATE
train,71,12,to,O
train,71,13,work,O
train,71,14,on,O
train,71,15,natural,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,71,16,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,71,17,processing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,71,18,.,O
train,72,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
train,72,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
train,72,3,presented,O
train,72,4,a,O
train,72,5,project,O
train,72,6,on,O
train,72,7,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,72,8,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,72,9,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,72,10,at,O
train,72,11,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,72,12,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,72,13,during,O
train,72,14,September,B-DATE
train,72,15,2026,I-DATE
train,72,16,.,O
train,73,1,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
train,73,2,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
train,73,3,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
train,73,4,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
train,73,5,announced,O
train,73,6,a,O
train,73,7,new,O
train,73,8,deep,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,73,9,learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,73,10,team,O
train,73,11,in,O
train,73,12,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
train,73,13,Lahore,I-LOCATION
train,73,14,on,O
train,73,15,1,B-DATE
train,73,16,August,I-DATE
train,73,17,2026,I-DATE
train,73,18,.,O
train,74,1,Ayesha,B-PERSON
train,74,2,Khan,I-PERSON
train,74,3,is,O
train,74,4,an,O
train,74,5,engineer,O
train,74,6,from,O
train,74,7,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,74,8,with,O
train,74,9,experience,O
train,74,10,in,O
train,74,11,deep,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,74,12,learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,74,13,.,O
train,75,1,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,75,2,is,O
train,75,3,hiring,O
train,75,4,graduates,O
train,75,5,skilled,O
train,75,6,in,O
train,75,7,transformer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,75,8,architecture,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,75,9,for,O
train,75,10,its,O
train,75,11,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,75,12,office,O
train,75,13,.,O
train,76,1,Danish,B-PERSON
train,76,2,Ali,I-PERSON
train,76,3,will,O
train,76,4,attend,O
train,76,5,an,O
train,76,6,interview,O
train,76,7,at,O
train,76,8,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
train,76,9,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
train,76,10,on,O
train,76,11,September,B-DATE
train,76,12,2026,I-DATE
train,76,13,.,O
train,77,1,The,O
train,77,2,named,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,77,3,entity,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,77,4,recognition,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,77,5,system,O
train,77,6,was,O
train,77,7,developed,O
train,77,8,by,O
train,77,9,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,77,10,in,O
train,77,11,Lahore,B-LOCATION
train,77,12,.,O
train,78,1,Sana,B-PERSON
train,78,2,Javed,I-PERSON
train,78,3,used,O
train,78,4,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,78,5,to,O
train,78,6,improve,O
train,78,7,a,O
train,78,8,product,O
train,78,9,built,O
train,78,10,for,O
train,78,11,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
train,78,12,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,78,13,.,O
train,79,1,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
train,79,2,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
train,79,3,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
train,79,4,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
train,79,5,released,O
train,79,6,its,O
train,79,7,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,79,8,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,79,9,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,79,10,research,O
train,79,11,report,O
train,79,12,in,O
train,79,13,Monday,B-DATE
train,79,14,.,O
train,80,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
train,80,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
train,80,3,moved,O
train,80,4,to,O
train,80,5,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,80,6,in,O
train,80,7,next,B-DATE
train,80,8,Friday,I-DATE
train,80,9,and,O
train,80,10,started,O
train,80,11,learning,O
train,80,12,computer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,80,13,vision,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,80,14,.,O
train,81,1,Maryam,B-PERSON
train,81,2,Tariq,I-PERSON
train,81,3,joined,O
train,81,4,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,81,5,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
train,81,6,in,O
train,81,7,Dubai,B-LOCATION
train,81,8,on,O
train,81,9,October,B-DATE
train,81,10,2026,I-DATE
train,81,11,to,O
train,81,12,work,O
train,81,13,on,O
train,81,14,MLOps,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,81,15,.,O
train,82,1,Ali,B-PERSON
train,82,2,Raza,I-PERSON
train,82,3,presented,O
train,82,4,a,O
train,82,5,project,O
train,82,6,on,O
train,82,7,REST,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,82,8,API,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,82,9,at,O
train,82,10,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,82,11,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,82,12,during,O
train,82,13,September,B-DATE
train,82,14,2026,I-DATE
train,82,15,.,O
train,83,1,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
train,83,2,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
train,83,3,announced,O
train,83,4,a,O
train,83,5,new,O
train,83,6,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,83,7,team,O
train,83,8,in,O
train,83,9,Doha,B-LOCATION
train,83,10,on,O
train,83,11,Monday,B-DATE
train,83,12,.,O
train,84,1,Bilal,B-PERSON
train,84,2,Hussain,I-PERSON
train,84,3,is,O
train,84,4,an,O
train,84,5,engineer,O
train,84,6,from,O
train,84,7,Silicon,B-LOCATION
train,84,8,Valley,I-LOCATION
train,84,9,with,O
train,84,10,experience,O
train,84,11,in,O
train,84,12,named,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,84,13,entity,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,84,14,recognition,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,84,15,.,O
train,85,1,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
train,85,2,is,O
train,85,3,hiring,O
train,85,4,graduates,O
train,85,5,skilled,O
train,85,6,in,O
train,85,7,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,85,8,for,O
train,85,9,its,O
train,85,10,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,85,11,office,O
train,85,12,.,O
train,86,1,Mehwish,B-PERSON
train,86,2,Akhtar,I-PERSON
train,86,3,will,O
train,86,4,attend,O
train,86,5,an,O
train,86,6,interview,O
train,86,7,at,O
train,86,8,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,86,9,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,86,10,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,86,11,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,86,12,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,86,13,on,O
train,86,14,September,B-DATE
train,86,15,2026,I-DATE
train,86,16,.,O
train,87,1,The,O
train,87,2,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,87,3,system,O
train,87,4,was,O
train,87,5,developed,O
train,87,6,by,O
train,87,7,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,87,8,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,87,9,in,O
train,87,10,United,B-LOCATION
train,87,11,Arab,I-LOCATION
train,87,12,Emirates,I-LOCATION
train,87,13,.,O
train,88,1,Maryam,B-PERSON
train,88,2,Tariq,I-PERSON
train,88,3,used,O
train,88,4,computer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,88,5,vision,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,88,6,to,O
train,88,7,improve,O
train,88,8,a,O
train,88,9,product,O
train,88,10,built,O
train,88,11,for,O
train,88,12,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
train,88,13,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
train,88,14,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
train,88,15,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
train,88,16,.,O
train,89,1,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
train,89,2,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
train,89,3,released,O
train,89,4,its,O
train,89,5,multi,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,89,6,agent,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,89,7,systems,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,89,8,research,O
train,89,9,report,O
train,89,10,in,O
train,89,11,15,B-DATE
train,89,12,July,I-DATE
train,89,13,2026,I-DATE
train,89,14,.,O
train,90,1,Mehwish,B-PERSON
train,90,2,Akhtar,I-PERSON
train,90,3,moved,O
train,90,4,to,O
train,90,5,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,90,6,in,O
train,90,7,March,B-DATE
train,90,8,2026,I-DATE
train,90,9,and,O
train,90,10,started,O
train,90,11,learning,O
train,90,12,data,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,90,13,preprocessing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,90,14,.,O
train,91,1,Hamza,B-PERSON
train,91,2,Siddiqui,I-PERSON
train,91,3,joined,O
train,91,4,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,91,5,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,91,6,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,91,7,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,91,8,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,91,9,in,O
train,91,10,Dubai,B-LOCATION
train,91,11,on,O
train,91,12,Monday,B-DATE
train,91,13,to,O
train,91,14,work,O
train,91,15,on,O
train,91,16,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,91,17,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,91,18,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,91,19,.,O
train,92,1,Bilal,B-PERSON
train,92,2,Hussain,I-PERSON
train,92,3,presented,O
train,92,4,a,O
train,92,5,project,O
train,92,6,on,O
train,92,7,natural,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,92,8,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,92,9,processing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,92,10,at,O
train,92,11,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,92,12,during,O
train,92,13,March,B-DATE
train,92,14,2026,I-DATE
train,92,15,.,O
train,93,1,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
train,93,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,93,3,announced,O
train,93,4,a,O
train,93,5,new,O
train,93,6,BIO,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,93,7,tagging,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,93,8,team,O
train,93,9,in,O
train,93,10,Abu,B-LOCATION
train,93,11,Dhabi,I-LOCATION
train,93,12,on,O
train,93,13,April,B-DATE
train,93,14,2025,I-DATE
train,93,15,.,O
train,94,1,Ayesha,B-PERSON
train,94,2,Khan,I-PERSON
train,94,3,is,O
train,94,4,an,O
train,94,5,engineer,O
train,94,6,from,O
train,94,7,Dubai,B-LOCATION
train,94,8,with,O
train,94,9,experience,O
train,94,10,in,O
train,94,11,computer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,94,12,vision,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,94,13,.,O
train,95,1,Arbisoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,95,2,is,O
train,95,3,hiring,O
train,95,4,graduates,O
train,95,5,skilled,O
train,95,6,in,O
train,95,7,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,95,8,for,O
train,95,9,its,O
train,95,10,Saudi,B-LOCATION
train,95,11,Arabia,I-LOCATION
train,95,12,office,O
train,95,13,.,O
train,96,1,Sana,B-PERSON
train,96,2,Javed,I-PERSON
train,96,3,will,O
train,96,4,attend,O
train,96,5,an,O
train,96,6,interview,O
train,96,7,at,O
train,96,8,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,96,9,on,O
train,96,10,15,B-DATE
train,96,11,July,I-DATE
train,96,12,2026,I-DATE
train,96,13,.,O
train,97,1,The,O
train,97,2,prompt,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,97,3,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,97,4,system,O
train,97,5,was,O
train,97,6,developed,O
train,97,7,by,O
train,97,8,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,97,9,in,O
train,97,10,Lahore,B-LOCATION
train,97,11,.,O
train,98,1,Saad,B-PERSON
train,98,2,Qureshi,I-PERSON
train,98,3,used,O
train,98,4,computer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,98,5,vision,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,98,6,to,O
train,98,7,improve,O
train,98,8,a,O
train,98,9,product,O
train,98,10,built,O
train,98,11,for,O
train,98,12,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,98,13,.,O
train,99,1,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,99,2,released,O
train,99,3,its,O
train,99,4,natural,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,99,5,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,99,6,processing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,99,7,research,O
train,99,8,report,O
train,99,9,in,O
train,99,10,October,B-DATE
train,99,11,2026,I-DATE
train,99,12,.,O
train,100,1,Hira,B-PERSON
train,100,2,Shah,I-PERSON
train,100,3,moved,O
train,100,4,to,O
train,100,5,United,B-LOCATION
train,100,6,Arab,I-LOCATION
train,100,7,Emirates,I-LOCATION
train,100,8,in,O
train,100,9,Monday,B-DATE
train,100,10,and,O
train,100,11,started,O
train,100,12,learning,O
train,100,13,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,100,14,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,100,15,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,100,16,.,O
train,101,1,Sara,B-PERSON
train,101,2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
train,101,3,joined,O
train,101,4,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
train,101,5,in,O
train,101,6,Johar,B-LOCATION
train,101,7,Town,I-LOCATION
train,101,8,on,O
train,101,9,1,B-DATE
train,101,10,August,I-DATE
train,101,11,2026,I-DATE
train,101,12,to,O
train,101,13,work,O
train,101,14,on,O
train,101,15,PyTorch,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,101,16,.,O
train,102,1,Mahnoor,B-PERSON
train,102,2,Rehman,I-PERSON
train,102,3,presented,O
train,102,4,a,O
train,102,5,project,O
train,102,6,on,O
train,102,7,transformer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,102,8,architecture,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,102,9,at,O
train,102,10,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,102,11,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,102,12,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,102,13,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,102,14,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,102,15,during,O
train,102,16,October,B-DATE
train,102,17,2026,I-DATE
train,102,18,.,O
train,104,1,Jamal,B-PERSON
train,104,2,Masood,I-PERSON
train,104,3,is,O
train,104,4,an,O
train,104,5,engineer,O
train,104,6,from,O
train,104,7,Saudi,B-LOCATION
train,104,8,Arabia,I-LOCATION
train,104,9,with,O
train,104,10,experience,O
train,104,11,in,O
train,104,12,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,104,13,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,104,14,.,O
train,105,1,National,B-ORGANIZATION
train,105,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,105,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,105,4,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,105,5,and,I-ORGANIZATION
train,105,6,Technology,I-ORGANIZATION
train,105,7,is,O
train,105,8,hiring,O
train,105,9,graduates,O
train,105,10,skilled,O
train,105,11,in,O
train,105,12,multi,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,105,13,agent,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,105,14,systems,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,105,15,for,O
train,105,16,its,O
train,105,17,United,B-LOCATION
train,105,18,Arab,I-LOCATION
train,105,19,Emirates,I-LOCATION
train,105,20,office,O
train,105,21,.,O
train,106,1,Zainab,B-PERSON
train,106,2,Iqbal,I-PERSON
train,106,3,will,O
train,106,4,attend,O
train,106,5,an,O
train,106,6,interview,O
train,106,7,at,O
train,106,8,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,106,9,on,O
train,106,10,5,B-DATE
train,106,11,May,I-DATE
train,106,12,2026,I-DATE
train,106,13,.,O
train,107,1,The,O
train,107,2,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,107,3,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,107,4,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,107,5,system,O
train,107,6,was,O
train,107,7,developed,O
train,107,8,by,O
train,107,9,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,107,10,in,O
train,107,11,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
train,107,12,Lahore,I-LOCATION
train,107,13,.,O
train,108,1,Zainab,B-PERSON
train,108,2,Iqbal,I-PERSON
train,108,3,used,O
train,108,4,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,108,5,to,O
train,108,6,improve,O
train,108,7,a,O
train,108,8,product,O
train,108,9,built,O
train,108,10,for,O
train,108,11,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,108,12,.,O
train,109,1,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,109,2,released,O
train,109,3,its,O
train,109,4,transformer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,109,5,architecture,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,109,6,research,O
train,109,7,report,O
train,109,8,in,O
train,109,9,5,B-DATE
train,109,10,May,I-DATE
train,109,11,2026,I-DATE
train,109,12,.,O
train,110,1,Zainab,B-PERSON
train,110,2,Iqbal,I-PERSON
train,110,3,moved,O
train,110,4,to,O
train,110,5,United,B-LOCATION
train,110,6,Arab,I-LOCATION
train,110,7,Emirates,I-LOCATION
train,110,8,in,O
train,110,9,Monday,B-DATE
train,110,10,and,O
train,110,11,started,O
train,110,12,learning,O
train,110,13,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,110,14,.,O
train,111,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
train,111,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
train,111,3,joined,O
train,111,4,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,111,5,in,O
train,111,6,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
train,111,7,Lahore,I-LOCATION
train,111,8,on,O
train,111,9,15,B-DATE
train,111,10,July,I-DATE
train,111,11,2026,I-DATE
train,111,12,to,O
train,111,13,work,O
train,111,14,on,O
train,111,15,MLOps,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,111,16,.,O
train,112,1,Bilal,B-PERSON
train,112,2,Hussain,I-PERSON
train,112,3,presented,O
train,112,4,a,O
train,112,5,project,O
train,112,6,on,O
train,112,7,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,112,8,at,O
train,112,9,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
train,112,10,during,O
train,112,11,1,B-DATE
train,112,12,August,I-DATE
train,112,13,2026,I-DATE
train,112,14,.,O
train,113,1,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
train,113,2,announced,O
train,113,3,a,O
train,113,4,new,O
train,113,5,BIO,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,113,6,tagging,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,113,7,team,O
train,113,8,in,O
train,113,9,Lahore,B-LOCATION
train,113,10,on,O
train,113,11,15,B-DATE
train,113,12,July,I-DATE
train,113,13,2026,I-DATE
train,113,14,.,O
train,114,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
train,114,2,Noor,I-PERSON
train,114,3,is,O
train,114,4,an,O
train,114,5,engineer,O
train,114,6,from,O
train,114,7,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,114,8,with,O
train,114,9,experience,O
train,114,10,in,O
train,114,11,large,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,114,12,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,114,13,models,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,114,14,.,O
train,115,1,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,115,2,is,O
train,115,3,hiring,O
train,115,4,graduates,O
train,115,5,skilled,O
train,115,6,in,O
train,115,7,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,115,8,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,115,9,for,O
train,115,10,its,O
train,115,11,Dubai,B-LOCATION
train,115,12,office,O
train,115,13,.,O
train,116,1,Sana,B-PERSON
train,116,2,Javed,I-PERSON
train,116,3,will,O
train,116,4,attend,O
train,116,5,an,O
train,116,6,interview,O
train,116,7,at,O
train,116,8,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,116,9,on,O
train,116,10,15,B-DATE
train,116,11,July,I-DATE
train,116,12,2026,I-DATE
train,116,13,.,O
train,117,1,The,O
train,117,2,semantic,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,117,3,search,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,117,4,system,O
train,117,5,was,O
train,117,6,developed,O
train,117,7,by,O
train,117,8,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,117,9,in,O
train,117,10,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,117,11,.,O
train,118,1,Sana,B-PERSON
train,118,2,Javed,I-PERSON
train,118,3,used,O
train,118,4,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,118,5,to,O
train,118,6,improve,O
train,118,7,a,O
train,118,8,product,O
train,118,9,built,O
train,118,10,for,O
train,118,11,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,118,12,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,118,13,.,O
train,119,1,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
train,119,2,released,O
train,119,3,its,O
train,119,4,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,119,5,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,119,6,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,119,7,research,O
train,119,8,report,O
train,119,9,in,O
train,119,10,15,B-DATE
train,119,11,July,I-DATE
train,119,12,2026,I-DATE
train,119,13,.,O
train,120,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
train,120,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
train,120,3,moved,O
train,120,4,to,O
train,120,5,Dubai,B-LOCATION
train,120,6,in,O
train,120,7,today,B-DATE
train,120,8,and,O
train,120,9,started,O
train,120,10,learning,O
train,120,11,large,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,120,12,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,120,13,models,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,120,14,.,O
train,121,1,Maryam,B-PERSON
train,121,2,Tariq,I-PERSON
train,121,3,joined,O
train,121,4,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,121,5,in,O
train,121,6,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,121,7,on,O
train,121,8,today,B-DATE
train,121,9,to,O
train,121,10,work,O
train,121,11,on,O
train,121,12,PyTorch,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,121,13,.,O
train,122,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
train,122,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
train,122,3,presented,O
train,122,4,a,O
train,122,5,project,O
train,122,6,on,O
train,122,7,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,122,8,at,O
train,122,9,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,122,10,during,O
train,122,11,March,B-DATE
train,122,12,2026,I-DATE
train,122,13,.,O
train,123,1,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,123,2,announced,O
train,123,3,a,O
train,123,4,new,O
train,123,5,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,123,6,team,O
train,123,7,in,O
train,123,8,Abu,B-LOCATION
train,123,9,Dhabi,I-LOCATION
train,123,10,on,O
train,123,11,today,B-DATE
train,123,12,.,O
train,124,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
train,124,2,Noor,I-PERSON
train,124,3,is,O
train,124,4,an,O
train,124,5,engineer,O
train,124,6,from,O
train,124,7,Pakistan,B-LOCATION
train,124,8,with,O
train,124,9,experience,O
train,124,10,in,O
train,124,11,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,124,12,.,O
train,125,1,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
train,125,2,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
train,125,3,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
train,125,4,is,O
train,125,5,hiring,O
train,125,6,graduates,O
train,125,7,skilled,O
train,125,8,in,O
train,125,9,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,125,10,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,125,11,for,O
train,125,12,its,O
train,125,13,Lahore,B-LOCATION
train,125,14,office,O
train,125,15,.,O
train,126,1,Hamza,B-PERSON
train,126,2,Siddiqui,I-PERSON
train,126,3,will,O
train,126,4,attend,O
train,126,5,an,O
train,126,6,interview,O
train,126,7,at,O
train,126,8,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,126,9,on,O
train,126,10,September,B-DATE
train,126,11,2026,I-DATE
train,126,12,.,O
train,127,1,The,O
train,127,2,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,127,3,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,127,4,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,127,5,system,O
train,127,6,was,O
train,127,7,developed,O
train,127,8,by,O
train,127,9,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,127,10,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
train,127,11,in,O
train,127,12,Riyadh,B-LOCATION
train,127,13,.,O
train,128,1,Hamza,B-PERSON
train,128,2,Siddiqui,I-PERSON
train,128,3,used,O
train,128,4,multi,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,128,5,agent,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,128,6,systems,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,128,7,to,O
train,128,8,improve,O
train,128,9,a,O
train,128,10,product,O
train,128,11,built,O
train,128,12,for,O
train,128,13,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,128,14,.,O
train,129,1,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
train,129,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,129,3,released,O
train,129,4,its,O
train,129,5,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,129,6,research,O
train,129,7,report,O
train,129,8,in,O
train,129,9,March,B-DATE
train,129,10,2026,I-DATE
train,129,11,.,O
train,130,1,Mahnoor,B-PERSON
train,130,2,Rehman,I-PERSON
train,130,3,moved,O
train,130,4,to,O
train,130,5,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,130,6,in,O
train,130,7,April,B-DATE
train,130,8,2025,I-DATE
train,130,9,and,O
train,130,10,started,O
train,130,11,learning,O
train,130,12,MLOps,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,130,13,.,O
train,131,1,Zainab,B-PERSON
train,131,2,Iqbal,I-PERSON
train,131,3,joined,O
train,131,4,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
train,131,5,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,131,6,in,O
train,131,7,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,131,8,on,O
train,131,9,Monday,B-DATE
train,131,10,to,O
train,131,11,work,O
train,131,12,on,O
train,131,13,retrieval,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,131,14,augmented,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,131,15,generation,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,131,16,.,O
train,132,1,Usman,B-PERSON
train,132,2,Malik,I-PERSON
train,132,3,presented,O
train,132,4,a,O
train,132,5,project,O
train,132,6,on,O
train,132,7,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,132,8,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,132,9,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,132,10,at,O
train,132,11,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,132,12,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,132,13,during,O
train,132,14,Monday,B-DATE
train,132,15,.,O
train,133,1,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
train,133,2,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
train,133,3,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
train,133,4,announced,O
train,133,5,a,O
train,133,6,new,O
train,133,7,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,133,8,team,O
train,133,9,in,O
train,133,10,Johar,B-LOCATION
train,133,11,Town,I-LOCATION
train,133,12,on,O
train,133,13,15,B-DATE
train,133,14,July,I-DATE
train,133,15,2026,I-DATE
train,133,16,.,O
train,134,1,Sana,B-PERSON
train,134,2,Javed,I-PERSON
train,134,3,is,O
train,134,4,an,O
train,134,5,engineer,O
train,134,6,from,O
train,134,7,United,B-LOCATION
train,134,8,Arab,I-LOCATION
train,134,9,Emirates,I-LOCATION
train,134,10,with,O
train,134,11,experience,O
train,134,12,in,O
train,134,13,retrieval,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,134,14,augmented,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,134,15,generation,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,134,16,.,O
train,135,1,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,135,2,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
train,135,3,is,O
train,135,4,hiring,O
train,135,5,graduates,O
train,135,6,skilled,O
train,135,7,in,O
train,135,8,computer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,135,9,vision,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,135,10,for,O
train,135,11,its,O
train,135,12,Abu,B-LOCATION
train,135,13,Dhabi,I-LOCATION
train,135,14,office,O
train,135,15,.,O
train,136,1,Jamal,B-PERSON
train,136,2,Masood,I-PERSON
train,136,3,will,O
train,136,4,attend,O
train,136,5,an,O
train,136,6,interview,O
train,136,7,at,O
train,136,8,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
train,136,9,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
train,136,10,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
train,136,11,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
train,136,12,on,O
train,136,13,April,B-DATE
train,136,14,2025,I-DATE
train,136,15,.,O
train,138,1,Talha,B-PERSON
train,138,2,Saeed,I-PERSON
train,138,3,used,O
train,138,4,transformer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,138,5,architecture,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,138,6,to,O
train,138,7,improve,O
train,138,8,a,O
train,138,9,product,O
train,138,10,built,O
train,138,11,for,O
train,138,12,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,138,13,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
train,138,14,.,O
train,139,1,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,139,2,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
train,139,3,released,O
train,139,4,its,O
train,139,5,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,139,6,research,O
train,139,7,report,O
train,139,8,in,O
train,139,9,5,B-DATE
train,139,10,May,I-DATE
train,139,11,2026,I-DATE
train,139,12,.,O
train,140,1,Talha,B-PERSON
train,140,2,Saeed,I-PERSON
train,140,3,moved,O
train,140,4,to,O
train,140,5,Pakistan,B-LOCATION
train,140,6,in,O
train,140,7,26,B-DATE
train,140,8,June,I-DATE
train,140,9,2026,I-DATE
train,140,10,and,O
train,140,11,started,O
train,140,12,learning,O
train,140,13,MLOps,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,140,14,.,O
train,141,1,Omar,B-PERSON
train,141,2,Farooq,I-PERSON
train,141,3,joined,O
train,141,4,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,141,5,in,O
train,141,6,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
train,141,7,Lahore,I-LOCATION
train,141,8,on,O
train,141,9,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,141,10,to,O
train,141,11,work,O
train,141,12,on,O
train,141,13,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,141,14,.,O
train,142,1,Sana,B-PERSON
train,142,2,Javed,I-PERSON
train,142,3,presented,O
train,142,4,a,O
train,142,5,project,O
train,142,6,on,O
train,142,7,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,142,8,at,O
train,142,9,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
train,142,10,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
train,142,11,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
train,142,12,during,O
train,142,13,1,B-DATE
train,142,14,August,I-DATE
train,142,15,2026,I-DATE
train,142,16,.,O
train,143,1,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,143,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,143,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,143,4,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,143,5,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,143,6,announced,O
train,143,7,a,O
train,143,8,new,O
train,143,9,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,143,10,team,O
train,143,11,in,O
train,143,12,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
train,143,13,Lahore,I-LOCATION
train,143,14,on,O
train,143,15,December,B-DATE
train,143,16,2025,I-DATE
train,143,17,.,O
train,144,1,Bilal,B-PERSON
train,144,2,Hussain,I-PERSON
train,144,3,is,O
train,144,4,an,O
train,144,5,engineer,O
train,144,6,from,O
train,144,7,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,144,8,with,O
train,144,9,experience,O
train,144,10,in,O
train,144,11,feature,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,144,12,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,144,13,.,O
train,145,1,National,B-ORGANIZATION
train,145,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,145,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,145,4,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,145,5,and,I-ORGANIZATION
train,145,6,Technology,I-ORGANIZATION
train,145,7,is,O
train,145,8,hiring,O
train,145,9,graduates,O
train,145,10,skilled,O
train,145,11,in,O
train,145,12,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,145,13,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,145,14,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,145,15,for,O
train,145,16,its,O
train,145,17,Johar,B-LOCATION
train,145,18,Town,I-LOCATION
train,145,19,office,O
train,145,20,.,O
train,146,1,Zainab,B-PERSON
train,146,2,Iqbal,I-PERSON
train,146,3,will,O
train,146,4,attend,O
train,146,5,an,O
train,146,6,interview,O
train,146,7,at,O
train,146,8,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,146,9,on,O
train,146,10,15,B-DATE
train,146,11,July,I-DATE
train,146,12,2026,I-DATE
train,146,13,.,O
train,147,1,The,O
train,147,2,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,147,3,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,147,4,system,O
train,147,5,was,O
train,147,6,developed,O
train,147,7,by,O
train,147,8,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,147,9,in,O
train,147,10,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,147,11,.,O
train,148,1,Mehwish,B-PERSON
train,148,2,Akhtar,I-PERSON
train,148,3,used,O
train,148,4,transformer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,148,5,architecture,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,148,6,to,O
train,148,7,improve,O
train,148,8,a,O
train,148,9,product,O
train,148,10,built,O
train,148,11,for,O
train,148,12,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
train,148,13,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
train,148,14,.,O
train,149,1,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,149,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,149,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,149,4,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,149,5,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,149,6,released,O
train,149,7,its,O
train,149,8,retrieval,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,149,9,augmented,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,149,10,generation,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,149,11,research,O
train,149,12,report,O
train,149,13,in,O
train,149,14,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,149,15,.,O
train,150,1,Ali,B-PERSON
train,150,2,Raza,I-PERSON
train,150,3,moved,O
train,150,4,to,O
train,150,5,Abu,B-LOCATION
train,150,6,Dhabi,I-LOCATION
train,150,7,in,O
train,150,8,26,B-DATE
train,150,9,June,I-DATE
train,150,10,2026,I-DATE
train,150,11,and,O
train,150,12,started,O
train,150,13,learning,O
train,150,14,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,150,15,.,O
train,151,1,Omar,B-PERSON
train,151,2,Farooq,I-PERSON
train,151,3,joined,O
train,151,4,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,151,5,in,O
train,151,6,Lahore,B-LOCATION
train,151,7,on,O
train,151,8,Monday,B-DATE
train,151,9,to,O
train,151,10,work,O
train,151,11,on,O
train,151,12,PyTorch,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,151,13,.,O
train,152,1,Danish,B-PERSON
train,152,2,Ali,I-PERSON
train,152,3,presented,O
train,152,4,a,O
train,152,5,project,O
train,152,6,on,O
train,152,7,semantic,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,152,8,search,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,152,9,at,O
train,152,10,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
train,152,11,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
train,152,12,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
train,152,13,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
train,152,14,during,O
train,152,15,September,B-DATE
train,152,16,2026,I-DATE
train,152,17,.,O
train,153,1,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
train,153,2,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
train,153,3,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
train,153,4,announced,O
train,153,5,a,O
train,153,6,new,O
train,153,7,REST,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,153,8,API,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,153,9,team,O
train,153,10,in,O
train,153,11,Silicon,B-LOCATION
train,153,12,Valley,I-LOCATION
train,153,13,on,O
train,153,14,5,B-DATE
train,153,15,May,I-DATE
train,153,16,2026,I-DATE
train,153,17,.,O
train,154,1,Danish,B-PERSON
train,154,2,Ali,I-PERSON
train,154,3,is,O
train,154,4,an,O
train,154,5,engineer,O
train,154,6,from,O
train,154,7,Lahore,B-LOCATION
train,154,8,with,O
train,154,9,experience,O
train,154,10,in,O
train,154,11,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,154,12,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,154,13,.,O
train,155,1,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
train,155,2,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
train,155,3,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
train,155,4,is,O
train,155,5,hiring,O
train,155,6,graduates,O
train,155,7,skilled,O
train,155,8,in,O
train,155,9,PyTorch,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,155,10,for,O
train,155,11,its,O
train,155,12,Silicon,B-LOCATION
train,155,13,Valley,I-LOCATION
train,155,14,office,O
train,155,15,.,O
train,156,1,Mehwish,B-PERSON
train,156,2,Akhtar,I-PERSON
train,156,3,will,O
train,156,4,attend,O
train,156,5,an,O
train,156,6,interview,O
train,156,7,at,O
train,156,8,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,156,9,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,156,10,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,156,11,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,156,12,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,156,13,on,O
train,156,14,1,B-DATE
train,156,15,August,I-DATE
train,156,16,2026,I-DATE
train,156,17,.,O
train,157,1,The,O
train,157,2,PyTorch,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,157,3,system,O
train,157,4,was,O
train,157,5,developed,O
train,157,6,by,O
train,157,7,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,157,8,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
train,157,9,in,O
train,157,10,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,157,11,.,O
train,158,1,Nida,B-PERSON
train,158,2,Aslam,I-PERSON
train,158,3,used,O
train,158,4,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,158,5,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,158,6,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,158,7,to,O
train,158,8,improve,O
train,158,9,a,O
train,158,10,product,O
train,158,11,built,O
train,158,12,for,O
train,158,13,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,158,14,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,158,15,.,O
train,159,1,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,159,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,159,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,159,4,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,159,5,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,159,6,released,O
train,159,7,its,O
train,159,8,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,159,9,research,O
train,159,10,report,O
train,159,11,in,O
train,159,12,April,B-DATE
train,159,13,2025,I-DATE
train,159,14,.,O
train,160,1,Usman,B-PERSON
train,160,2,Malik,I-PERSON
train,160,3,moved,O
train,160,4,to,O
train,160,5,Doha,B-LOCATION
train,160,6,in,O
train,160,7,June,B-DATE
train,160,8,2026,I-DATE
train,160,9,and,O
train,160,10,started,O
train,160,11,learning,O
train,160,12,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,160,13,.,O
train,161,1,Saad,B-PERSON
train,161,2,Qureshi,I-PERSON
train,161,3,joined,O
train,161,4,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,161,5,in,O
train,161,6,United,B-LOCATION
train,161,7,Arab,I-LOCATION
train,161,8,Emirates,I-LOCATION
train,161,9,on,O
train,161,10,June,B-DATE
train,161,11,2026,I-DATE
train,161,12,to,O
train,161,13,work,O
train,161,14,on,O
train,161,15,named,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,161,16,entity,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,161,17,recognition,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,161,18,.,O
train,162,1,Sana,B-PERSON
train,162,2,Javed,I-PERSON
train,162,3,presented,O
train,162,4,a,O
train,162,5,project,O
train,162,6,on,O
train,162,7,deep,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,162,8,learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,162,9,at,O
train,162,10,Arbisoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,162,11,during,O
train,162,12,December,B-DATE
train,162,13,2025,I-DATE
train,162,14,.,O
train,163,1,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,163,2,announced,O
train,163,3,a,O
train,163,4,new,O
train,163,5,retrieval,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,163,6,augmented,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,163,7,generation,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,163,8,team,O
train,163,9,in,O
train,163,10,Abu,B-LOCATION
train,163,11,Dhabi,I-LOCATION
train,163,12,on,O
train,163,13,26,B-DATE
train,163,14,June,I-DATE
train,163,15,2026,I-DATE
train,163,16,.,O
train,164,1,Omar,B-PERSON
train,164,2,Farooq,I-PERSON
train,164,3,is,O
train,164,4,an,O
train,164,5,engineer,O
train,164,6,from,O
train,164,7,Dubai,B-LOCATION
train,164,8,with,O
train,164,9,experience,O
train,164,10,in,O
train,164,11,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,164,12,.,O
train,165,1,National,B-ORGANIZATION
train,165,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,165,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,165,4,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,165,5,and,I-ORGANIZATION
train,165,6,Technology,I-ORGANIZATION
train,165,7,is,O
train,165,8,hiring,O
train,165,9,graduates,O
train,165,10,skilled,O
train,165,11,in,O
train,165,12,BIO,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,165,13,tagging,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,165,14,for,O
train,165,15,its,O
train,165,16,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
train,165,17,Lahore,I-LOCATION
train,165,18,office,O
train,165,19,.,O
train,166,1,Ali,B-PERSON
train,166,2,Raza,I-PERSON
train,166,3,will,O
train,166,4,attend,O
train,166,5,an,O
train,166,6,interview,O
train,166,7,at,O
train,166,8,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,166,9,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
train,166,10,on,O
train,166,11,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,166,12,.,O
train,167,1,The,O
train,167,2,named,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,167,3,entity,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,167,4,recognition,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,167,5,system,O
train,167,6,was,O
train,167,7,developed,O
train,167,8,by,O
train,167,9,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
train,167,10,in,O
train,167,11,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,167,12,.,O
train,168,1,Ayesha,B-PERSON
train,168,2,Khan,I-PERSON
train,168,3,used,O
train,168,4,retrieval,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,168,5,augmented,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,168,6,generation,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,168,7,to,O
train,168,8,improve,O
train,168,9,a,O
train,168,10,product,O
train,168,11,built,O
train,168,12,for,O
train,168,13,National,B-ORGANIZATION
train,168,14,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,168,15,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,168,16,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,168,17,and,I-ORGANIZATION
train,168,18,Technology,I-ORGANIZATION
train,168,19,.,O
train,169,1,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,169,2,released,O
train,169,3,its,O
train,169,4,computer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,169,5,vision,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,169,6,research,O
train,169,7,report,O
train,169,8,in,O
train,169,9,Monday,B-DATE
train,169,10,.,O
train,170,1,Nida,B-PERSON
train,170,2,Aslam,I-PERSON
train,170,3,moved,O
train,170,4,to,O
train,170,5,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,170,6,in,O
train,170,7,September,B-DATE
train,170,8,2026,I-DATE
train,170,9,and,O
train,170,10,started,O
train,170,11,learning,O
train,170,12,retrieval,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,170,13,augmented,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,170,14,generation,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,170,15,.,O
train,171,1,Omar,B-PERSON
train,171,2,Farooq,I-PERSON
train,171,3,joined,O
train,171,4,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,171,5,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,171,6,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,171,7,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,171,8,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,171,9,in,O
train,171,10,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,171,11,on,O
train,171,12,5,B-DATE
train,171,13,May,I-DATE
train,171,14,2026,I-DATE
train,171,15,to,O
train,171,16,work,O
train,171,17,on,O
train,171,18,prompt,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,171,19,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,171,20,.,O
train,172,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
train,172,2,Noor,I-PERSON
train,172,3,presented,O
train,172,4,a,O
train,172,5,project,O
train,172,6,on,O
train,172,7,semantic,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,172,8,search,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,172,9,at,O
train,172,10,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,172,11,during,O
train,172,12,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,172,13,.,O
train,174,1,Sara,B-PERSON
train,174,2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
train,174,3,is,O
train,174,4,an,O
train,174,5,engineer,O
train,174,6,from,O
train,174,7,Lahore,B-LOCATION
train,174,8,with,O
train,174,9,experience,O
train,174,10,in,O
train,174,11,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,174,12,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,174,13,.,O
train,175,1,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
train,175,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,175,3,is,O
train,175,4,hiring,O
train,175,5,graduates,O
train,175,6,skilled,O
train,175,7,in,O
train,175,8,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,175,9,for,O
train,175,10,its,O
train,175,11,Silicon,B-LOCATION
train,175,12,Valley,I-LOCATION
train,175,13,office,O
train,175,14,.,O
train,176,1,Hamza,B-PERSON
train,176,2,Siddiqui,I-PERSON
train,176,3,will,O
train,176,4,attend,O
train,176,5,an,O
train,176,6,interview,O
train,176,7,at,O
train,176,8,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
train,176,9,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
train,176,10,on,O
train,176,11,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,176,12,.,O
train,177,1,The,O
train,177,2,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,177,3,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,177,4,system,O
train,177,5,was,O
train,177,6,developed,O
train,177,7,by,O
train,177,8,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
train,177,9,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
train,177,10,in,O
train,177,11,Saudi,B-LOCATION
train,177,12,Arabia,I-LOCATION
train,177,13,.,O
train,179,1,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
train,179,2,released,O
train,179,3,its,O
train,179,4,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,179,5,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,179,6,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,179,7,research,O
train,179,8,report,O
train,179,9,in,O
train,179,10,next,B-DATE
train,179,11,Friday,I-DATE
train,179,12,.,O
train,180,1,Hira,B-PERSON
train,180,2,Shah,I-PERSON
train,180,3,moved,O
train,180,4,to,O
train,180,5,Doha,B-LOCATION
train,180,6,in,O
train,180,7,today,B-DATE
train,180,8,and,O
train,180,9,started,O
train,180,10,learning,O
train,180,11,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,180,12,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,180,13,.,O
train,181,1,Jamal,B-PERSON
train,181,2,Masood,I-PERSON
train,181,3,joined,O
train,181,4,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
train,181,5,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
train,181,6,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
train,181,7,in,O
train,181,8,Abu,B-LOCATION
train,181,9,Dhabi,I-LOCATION
train,181,10,on,O
train,181,11,April,B-DATE
train,181,12,2025,I-DATE
train,181,13,to,O
train,181,14,work,O
train,181,15,on,O
train,181,16,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,181,17,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,181,18,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,181,19,.,O
train,182,1,Sara,B-PERSON
train,182,2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
train,182,3,presented,O
train,182,4,a,O
train,182,5,project,O
train,182,6,on,O
train,182,7,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,182,8,at,O
train,182,9,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,182,10,during,O
train,182,11,today,B-DATE
train,182,12,.,O
train,183,1,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
train,183,2,announced,O
train,183,3,a,O
train,183,4,new,O
train,183,5,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,183,6,team,O
train,183,7,in,O
train,183,8,Islamabad,B-LOCATION
train,183,9,on,O
train,183,10,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,183,11,.,O
train,184,1,Bilal,B-PERSON
train,184,2,Hussain,I-PERSON
train,184,3,is,O
train,184,4,an,O
train,184,5,engineer,O
train,184,6,from,O
train,184,7,Johar,B-LOCATION
train,184,8,Town,I-LOCATION
train,184,9,with,O
train,184,10,experience,O
train,184,11,in,O
train,184,12,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,184,13,.,O
train,185,1,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,185,2,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
train,185,3,is,O
train,185,4,hiring,O
train,185,5,graduates,O
train,185,6,skilled,O
train,185,7,in,O
train,185,8,multi,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,185,9,agent,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,185,10,systems,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,185,11,for,O
train,185,12,its,O
train,185,13,Abu,B-LOCATION
train,185,14,Dhabi,I-LOCATION
train,185,15,office,O
train,185,16,.,O
train,186,1,Saad,B-PERSON
train,186,2,Qureshi,I-PERSON
train,186,3,will,O
train,186,4,attend,O
train,186,5,an,O
train,186,6,interview,O
train,186,7,at,O
train,186,8,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,186,9,on,O
train,186,10,April,B-DATE
train,186,11,2025,I-DATE
train,186,12,.,O
train,187,1,The,O
train,187,2,transformer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,187,3,architecture,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,187,4,system,O
train,187,5,was,O
train,187,6,developed,O
train,187,7,by,O
train,187,8,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,187,9,in,O
train,187,10,Silicon,B-LOCATION
train,187,11,Valley,I-LOCATION
train,187,12,.,O
train,188,1,Omar,B-PERSON
train,188,2,Farooq,I-PERSON
train,188,3,used,O
train,188,4,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,188,5,to,O
train,188,6,improve,O
train,188,7,a,O
train,188,8,product,O
train,188,9,built,O
train,188,10,for,O
train,188,11,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
train,188,12,.,O
train,189,1,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,189,2,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,189,3,released,O
train,189,4,its,O
train,189,5,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,189,6,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,189,7,research,O
train,189,8,report,O
train,189,9,in,O
train,189,10,April,B-DATE
train,189,11,2025,I-DATE
train,189,12,.,O
train,190,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
train,190,2,Noor,I-PERSON
train,190,3,moved,O
train,190,4,to,O
train,190,5,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,190,6,in,O
train,190,7,26,B-DATE
train,190,8,June,I-DATE
train,190,9,2026,I-DATE
train,190,10,and,O
train,190,11,started,O
train,190,12,learning,O
train,190,13,BIO,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,190,14,tagging,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,190,15,.,O
train,191,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
train,191,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
train,191,3,joined,O
train,191,4,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
train,191,5,in,O
train,191,6,Silicon,B-LOCATION
train,191,7,Valley,I-LOCATION
train,191,8,on,O
train,191,9,September,B-DATE
train,191,10,2026,I-DATE
train,191,11,to,O
train,191,12,work,O
train,191,13,on,O
train,191,14,semantic,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,191,15,search,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,191,16,.,O
train,192,1,Bilal,B-PERSON
train,192,2,Hussain,I-PERSON
train,192,3,presented,O
train,192,4,a,O
train,192,5,project,O
train,192,6,on,O
train,192,7,retrieval,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,192,8,augmented,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,192,9,generation,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,192,10,at,O
train,192,11,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,192,12,during,O
train,192,13,1,B-DATE
train,192,14,August,I-DATE
train,192,15,2026,I-DATE
train,192,16,.,O
train,193,1,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,193,2,announced,O
train,193,3,a,O
train,193,4,new,O
train,193,5,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,193,6,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,193,7,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,193,8,team,O
train,193,9,in,O
train,193,10,Saudi,B-LOCATION
train,193,11,Arabia,I-LOCATION
train,193,12,on,O
train,193,13,next,B-DATE
train,193,14,Friday,I-DATE
train,193,15,.,O
train,194,1,Mehwish,B-PERSON
train,194,2,Akhtar,I-PERSON
train,194,3,is,O
train,194,4,an,O
train,194,5,engineer,O
train,194,6,from,O
train,194,7,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
train,194,8,with,O
train,194,9,experience,O
train,194,10,in,O
train,194,11,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,194,12,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,194,13,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,194,14,.,O
train,195,1,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
train,195,2,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
train,195,3,is,O
train,195,4,hiring,O
train,195,5,graduates,O
train,195,6,skilled,O
train,195,7,in,O
train,195,8,named,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,195,9,entity,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,195,10,recognition,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,195,11,for,O
train,195,12,its,O
train,195,13,Johar,B-LOCATION
train,195,14,Town,I-LOCATION
train,195,15,office,O
train,195,16,.,O
train,196,1,Maryam,B-PERSON
train,196,2,Tariq,I-PERSON
train,196,3,will,O
train,196,4,attend,O
train,196,5,an,O
train,196,6,interview,O
train,196,7,at,O
train,196,8,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,196,9,on,O
train,196,10,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,196,11,.,O
train,197,1,The,O
train,197,2,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,197,3,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,197,4,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,197,5,system,O
train,197,6,was,O
train,197,7,developed,O
train,197,8,by,O
train,197,9,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
train,197,10,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,197,11,in,O
train,197,12,Pakistan,B-LOCATION
train,197,13,.,O
train,198,1,Mehwish,B-PERSON
train,198,2,Akhtar,I-PERSON
train,198,3,used,O
train,198,4,multi,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,198,5,agent,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,198,6,systems,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,198,7,to,O
train,198,8,improve,O
train,198,9,a,O
train,198,10,product,O
train,198,11,built,O
train,198,12,for,O
train,198,13,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
train,198,14,.,O
train,199,1,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
train,199,2,released,O
train,199,3,its,O
train,199,4,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,199,5,research,O
train,199,6,report,O
train,199,7,in,O
train,199,8,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,199,9,.,O
train,200,1,Bilal,B-PERSON
train,200,2,Hussain,I-PERSON
train,200,3,moved,O
train,200,4,to,O
train,200,5,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
train,200,6,in,O
train,200,7,Monday,B-DATE
train,200,8,and,O
train,200,9,started,O
train,200,10,learning,O
train,200,11,large,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,200,12,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,200,13,models,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,200,14,.,O
train,201,1,Hamza,B-PERSON
train,201,2,Siddiqui,I-PERSON
train,201,3,joined,O
train,201,4,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
train,201,5,in,O
train,201,6,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,201,7,on,O
train,201,8,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,201,9,to,O
train,201,10,work,O
train,201,11,on,O
train,201,12,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,201,13,.,O
train,202,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
train,202,2,Noor,I-PERSON
train,202,3,presented,O
train,202,4,a,O
train,202,5,project,O
train,202,6,on,O
train,202,7,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,202,8,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,202,9,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,202,10,at,O
train,202,11,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,202,12,during,O
train,202,13,tomorrow,B-DATE
train,202,14,.,O
train,203,1,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,203,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,203,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,203,4,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,203,5,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,203,6,announced,O
train,203,7,a,O
train,203,8,new,O
train,203,9,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,203,10,team,O
train,203,11,in,O
train,203,12,Pakistan,B-LOCATION
train,203,13,on,O
train,203,14,5,B-DATE
train,203,15,May,I-DATE
train,203,16,2026,I-DATE
train,203,17,.,O
train,204,1,Mahnoor,B-PERSON
train,204,2,Rehman,I-PERSON
train,204,3,is,O
train,204,4,an,O
train,204,5,engineer,O
train,204,6,from,O
train,204,7,Karachi,B-LOCATION
train,204,8,with,O
train,204,9,experience,O
train,204,10,in,O
train,204,11,retrieval,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,204,12,augmented,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,204,13,generation,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,204,14,.,O
train,205,1,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
train,205,2,is,O
train,205,3,hiring,O
train,205,4,graduates,O
train,205,5,skilled,O
train,205,6,in,O
train,205,7,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,205,8,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,205,9,for,O
train,205,10,its,O
train,205,11,Dubai,B-LOCATION
train,205,12,office,O
train,205,13,.,O
train,206,1,Jamal,B-PERSON
train,206,2,Masood,I-PERSON
train,206,3,will,O
train,206,4,attend,O
train,206,5,an,O
train,206,6,interview,O
train,206,7,at,O
train,206,8,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
train,206,9,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,206,10,of,I-ORGANIZATION
train,206,11,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
train,206,12,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
train,206,13,on,O
train,206,14,January,B-DATE
train,206,15,2025,I-DATE
train,206,16,.,O
train,207,1,The,O
train,207,2,semantic,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,207,3,search,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,207,4,system,O
train,207,5,was,O
train,207,6,developed,O
train,207,7,by,O
train,207,8,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
train,207,9,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
train,207,10,in,O
train,207,11,Doha,B-LOCATION
train,207,12,.,O
train,208,1,Usman,B-PERSON
train,208,2,Malik,I-PERSON
train,208,3,used,O
train,208,4,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,208,5,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,208,6,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,208,7,to,O
train,208,8,improve,O
train,208,9,a,O
train,208,10,product,O
train,208,11,built,O
train,208,12,for,O
train,208,13,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
train,208,14,University,I-ORGANIZATION
train,208,15,.,O
train,209,1,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
train,209,2,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
train,209,3,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
train,209,4,released,O
train,209,5,its,O
train,209,6,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,209,7,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,209,8,research,O
train,209,9,report,O
train,209,10,in,O
train,209,11,September,B-DATE
train,209,12,2026,I-DATE
train,209,13,.,O
train,210,1,Nida,B-PERSON
train,210,2,Aslam,I-PERSON
train,210,3,moved,O
train,210,4,to,O
train,210,5,Riyadh,B-LOCATION
train,210,6,in,O
train,210,7,26,B-DATE
train,210,8,June,I-DATE
train,210,9,2026,I-DATE
train,210,10,and,O
train,210,11,started,O
train,210,12,learning,O
train,210,13,deep,B-DOMAIN_TERM
train,210,14,learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
train,210,15,.,O
validation,211,1,Ayesha,B-PERSON
validation,211,2,Khan,I-PERSON
validation,211,3,joined,O
validation,211,4,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,211,5,in,O
validation,211,6,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
validation,211,7,Lahore,I-LOCATION
validation,211,8,on,O
validation,211,9,December,B-DATE
validation,211,10,2025,I-DATE
validation,211,11,to,O
validation,211,12,work,O
validation,211,13,on,O
validation,211,14,large,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,211,15,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,211,16,models,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,211,17,.,O
validation,212,1,Ali,B-PERSON
validation,212,2,Raza,I-PERSON
validation,212,3,presented,O
validation,212,4,a,O
validation,212,5,project,O
validation,212,6,on,O
validation,212,7,REST,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,212,8,API,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,212,9,at,O
validation,212,10,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,212,11,during,O
validation,212,12,15,B-DATE
validation,212,13,July,I-DATE
validation,212,14,2026,I-DATE
validation,212,15,.,O
validation,213,1,Arbisoft,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,213,2,announced,O
validation,213,3,a,O
validation,213,4,new,O
validation,213,5,REST,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,213,6,API,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,213,7,team,O
validation,213,8,in,O
validation,213,9,Islamabad,B-LOCATION
validation,213,10,on,O
validation,213,11,5,B-DATE
validation,213,12,May,I-DATE
validation,213,13,2026,I-DATE
validation,213,14,.,O
validation,214,1,Maryam,B-PERSON
validation,214,2,Tariq,I-PERSON
validation,214,3,is,O
validation,214,4,an,O
validation,214,5,engineer,O
validation,214,6,from,O
validation,214,7,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
validation,214,8,with,O
validation,214,9,experience,O
validation,214,10,in,O
validation,214,11,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,214,12,.,O
validation,215,1,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,215,2,is,O
validation,215,3,hiring,O
validation,215,4,graduates,O
validation,215,5,skilled,O
validation,215,6,in,O
validation,215,7,data,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,215,8,preprocessing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,215,9,for,O
validation,215,10,its,O
validation,215,11,Pakistan,B-LOCATION
validation,215,12,office,O
validation,215,13,.,O
validation,217,1,The,O
validation,217,2,PyTorch,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,217,3,system,O
validation,217,4,was,O
validation,217,5,developed,O
validation,217,6,by,O
validation,217,7,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,217,8,in,O
validation,217,9,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
validation,217,10,Lahore,I-LOCATION
validation,217,11,.,O
validation,218,1,Maryam,B-PERSON
validation,218,2,Tariq,I-PERSON
validation,218,3,used,O
validation,218,4,data,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,218,5,preprocessing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,218,6,to,O
validation,218,7,improve,O
validation,218,8,a,O
validation,218,9,product,O
validation,218,10,built,O
validation,218,11,for,O
validation,218,12,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,218,13,.,O
validation,220,1,Bilal,B-PERSON
validation,220,2,Hussain,I-PERSON
validation,220,3,moved,O
validation,220,4,to,O
validation,220,5,Karachi,B-LOCATION
validation,220,6,in,O
validation,220,7,January,B-DATE
validation,220,8,2025,I-DATE
validation,220,9,and,O
validation,220,10,started,O
validation,220,11,learning,O
validation,220,12,transformer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,220,13,architecture,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,220,14,.,O
validation,221,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
validation,221,2,Noor,I-PERSON
validation,221,3,joined,O
validation,221,4,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,221,5,in,O
validation,221,6,Karachi,B-LOCATION
validation,221,7,on,O
validation,221,8,January,B-DATE
validation,221,9,2025,I-DATE
validation,221,10,to,O
validation,221,11,work,O
validation,221,12,on,O
validation,221,13,machine,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,221,14,learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,221,15,.,O
validation,222,1,Sana,B-PERSON
validation,222,2,Javed,I-PERSON
validation,222,3,presented,O
validation,222,4,a,O
validation,222,5,project,O
validation,222,6,on,O
validation,222,7,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,222,8,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,222,9,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,222,10,at,O
validation,222,11,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,222,12,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,222,13,during,O
validation,222,14,September,B-DATE
validation,222,15,2026,I-DATE
validation,222,16,.,O
validation,223,1,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,223,2,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,223,3,announced,O
validation,223,4,a,O
validation,223,5,new,O
validation,223,6,semantic,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,223,7,search,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,223,8,team,O
validation,223,9,in,O
validation,223,10,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
validation,223,11,on,O
validation,223,12,March,B-DATE
validation,223,13,2026,I-DATE
validation,223,14,.,O
validation,224,1,Maryam,B-PERSON
validation,224,2,Tariq,I-PERSON
validation,224,3,is,O
validation,224,4,an,O
validation,224,5,engineer,O
validation,224,6,from,O
validation,224,7,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
validation,224,8,Lahore,I-LOCATION
validation,224,9,with,O
validation,224,10,experience,O
validation,224,11,in,O
validation,224,12,named,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,224,13,entity,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,224,14,recognition,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,224,15,.,O
validation,225,1,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,225,2,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,225,3,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,225,4,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,225,5,is,O
validation,225,6,hiring,O
validation,225,7,graduates,O
validation,225,8,skilled,O
validation,225,9,in,O
validation,225,10,feature,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,225,11,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,225,12,for,O
validation,225,13,its,O
validation,225,14,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
validation,225,15,office,O
validation,225,16,.,O
validation,226,1,Saad,B-PERSON
validation,226,2,Qureshi,I-PERSON
validation,226,3,will,O
validation,226,4,attend,O
validation,226,5,an,O
validation,226,6,interview,O
validation,226,7,at,O
validation,226,8,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,226,9,University,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,226,10,on,O
validation,226,11,October,B-DATE
validation,226,12,2026,I-DATE
validation,226,13,.,O
validation,227,1,The,O
validation,227,2,feature,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,227,3,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,227,4,system,O
validation,227,5,was,O
validation,227,6,developed,O
validation,227,7,by,O
validation,227,8,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,227,9,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,227,10,in,O
validation,227,11,Doha,B-LOCATION
validation,227,12,.,O
validation,228,1,Usman,B-PERSON
validation,228,2,Malik,I-PERSON
validation,228,3,used,O
validation,228,4,computer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,228,5,vision,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,228,6,to,O
validation,228,7,improve,O
validation,228,8,a,O
validation,228,9,product,O
validation,228,10,built,O
validation,228,11,for,O
validation,228,12,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,228,13,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,228,14,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,228,15,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,228,16,.,O
validation,229,1,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,229,2,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,229,3,released,O
validation,229,4,its,O
validation,229,5,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,229,6,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,229,7,research,O
validation,229,8,report,O
validation,229,9,in,O
validation,229,10,5,B-DATE
validation,229,11,May,I-DATE
validation,229,12,2026,I-DATE
validation,229,13,.,O
validation,230,1,Mahnoor,B-PERSON
validation,230,2,Rehman,I-PERSON
validation,230,3,moved,O
validation,230,4,to,O
validation,230,5,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
validation,230,6,Lahore,I-LOCATION
validation,230,7,in,O
validation,230,8,September,B-DATE
validation,230,9,2026,I-DATE
validation,230,10,and,O
validation,230,11,started,O
validation,230,12,learning,O
validation,230,13,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,230,14,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,230,15,.,O
validation,231,1,Omar,B-PERSON
validation,231,2,Farooq,I-PERSON
validation,231,3,joined,O
validation,231,4,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,231,5,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,231,6,in,O
validation,231,7,Riyadh,B-LOCATION
validation,231,8,on,O
validation,231,9,tomorrow,B-DATE
validation,231,10,to,O
validation,231,11,work,O
validation,231,12,on,O
validation,231,13,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,231,14,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,231,15,.,O
validation,232,1,Danish,B-PERSON
validation,232,2,Ali,I-PERSON
validation,232,3,presented,O
validation,232,4,a,O
validation,232,5,project,O
validation,232,6,on,O
validation,232,7,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,232,8,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,232,9,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,232,10,at,O
validation,232,11,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,232,12,during,O
validation,232,13,1,B-DATE
validation,232,14,August,I-DATE
validation,232,15,2026,I-DATE
validation,232,16,.,O
validation,233,1,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,233,2,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,233,3,announced,O
validation,233,4,a,O
validation,233,5,new,O
validation,233,6,PyTorch,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,233,7,team,O
validation,233,8,in,O
validation,233,9,Pakistan,B-LOCATION
validation,233,10,on,O
validation,233,11,June,B-DATE
validation,233,12,2026,I-DATE
validation,233,13,.,O
validation,234,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
validation,234,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
validation,234,3,is,O
validation,234,4,an,O
validation,234,5,engineer,O
validation,234,6,from,O
validation,234,7,Faisalabad,B-LOCATION
validation,234,8,with,O
validation,234,9,experience,O
validation,234,10,in,O
validation,234,11,named,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,234,12,entity,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,234,13,recognition,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,234,14,.,O
validation,235,1,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,235,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,235,3,is,O
validation,235,4,hiring,O
validation,235,5,graduates,O
validation,235,6,skilled,O
validation,235,7,in,O
validation,235,8,REST,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,235,9,API,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,235,10,for,O
validation,235,11,its,O
validation,235,12,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
validation,235,13,Lahore,I-LOCATION
validation,235,14,office,O
validation,235,15,.,O
validation,236,1,Saad,B-PERSON
validation,236,2,Qureshi,I-PERSON
validation,236,3,will,O
validation,236,4,attend,O
validation,236,5,an,O
validation,236,6,interview,O
validation,236,7,at,O
validation,236,8,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,236,9,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,236,10,on,O
validation,236,11,today,B-DATE
validation,236,12,.,O
validation,237,1,The,O
validation,237,2,deep,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,237,3,learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,237,4,system,O
validation,237,5,was,O
validation,237,6,developed,O
validation,237,7,by,O
validation,237,8,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,237,9,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,237,10,in,O
validation,237,11,Johar,B-LOCATION
validation,237,12,Town,I-LOCATION
validation,237,13,.,O
validation,238,1,Nida,B-PERSON
validation,238,2,Aslam,I-PERSON
validation,238,3,used,O
validation,238,4,BIO,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,238,5,tagging,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,238,6,to,O
validation,238,7,improve,O
validation,238,8,a,O
validation,238,9,product,O
validation,238,10,built,O
validation,238,11,for,O
validation,238,12,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,238,13,.,O
validation,239,1,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,239,2,released,O
validation,239,3,its,O
validation,239,4,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,239,5,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,239,6,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,239,7,research,O
validation,239,8,report,O
validation,239,9,in,O
validation,239,10,today,B-DATE
validation,239,11,.,O
validation,240,1,Ali,B-PERSON
validation,240,2,Raza,I-PERSON
validation,240,3,moved,O
validation,240,4,to,O
validation,240,5,Dubai,B-LOCATION
validation,240,6,in,O
validation,240,7,next,B-DATE
validation,240,8,Friday,I-DATE
validation,240,9,and,O
validation,240,10,started,O
validation,240,11,learning,O
validation,240,12,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,240,13,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,240,14,.,O
validation,241,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
validation,241,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
validation,241,3,joined,O
validation,241,4,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,241,5,University,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,241,6,in,O
validation,241,7,Karachi,B-LOCATION
validation,241,8,on,O
validation,241,9,April,B-DATE
validation,241,10,2025,I-DATE
validation,241,11,to,O
validation,241,12,work,O
validation,241,13,on,O
validation,241,14,deep,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,241,15,learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,241,16,.,O
validation,242,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
validation,242,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
validation,242,3,presented,O
validation,242,4,a,O
validation,242,5,project,O
validation,242,6,on,O
validation,242,7,token,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,242,8,classification,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,242,9,at,O
validation,242,10,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,242,11,during,O
validation,242,12,December,B-DATE
validation,242,13,2025,I-DATE
validation,242,14,.,O
validation,243,1,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,243,2,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,243,3,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,243,4,announced,O
validation,243,5,a,O
validation,243,6,new,O
validation,243,7,natural,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,243,8,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,243,9,processing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,243,10,team,O
validation,243,11,in,O
validation,243,12,Johar,B-LOCATION
validation,243,13,Town,I-LOCATION
validation,243,14,on,O
validation,243,15,1,B-DATE
validation,243,16,August,I-DATE
validation,243,17,2026,I-DATE
validation,243,18,.,O
validation,244,1,Omar,B-PERSON
validation,244,2,Farooq,I-PERSON
validation,244,3,is,O
validation,244,4,an,O
validation,244,5,engineer,O
validation,244,6,from,O
validation,244,7,Dubai,B-LOCATION
validation,244,8,with,O
validation,244,9,experience,O
validation,244,10,in,O
validation,244,11,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,244,12,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,244,13,.,O
validation,246,1,Jamal,B-PERSON
validation,246,2,Masood,I-PERSON
validation,246,3,will,O
validation,246,4,attend,O
validation,246,5,an,O
validation,246,6,interview,O
validation,246,7,at,O
validation,246,8,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,246,9,University,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,246,10,on,O
validation,246,11,1,B-DATE
validation,246,12,August,I-DATE
validation,246,13,2026,I-DATE
validation,246,14,.,O
validation,247,1,The,O
validation,247,2,prompt,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,247,3,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,247,4,system,O
validation,247,5,was,O
validation,247,6,developed,O
validation,247,7,by,O
validation,247,8,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,247,9,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,247,10,in,O
validation,247,11,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
validation,247,12,.,O
validation,249,1,Confiz,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,249,2,released,O
validation,249,3,its,O
validation,249,4,computer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,249,5,vision,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,249,6,research,O
validation,249,7,report,O
validation,249,8,in,O
validation,249,9,1,B-DATE
validation,249,10,August,I-DATE
validation,249,11,2026,I-DATE
validation,249,12,.,O
validation,250,1,Maryam,B-PERSON
validation,250,2,Tariq,I-PERSON
validation,250,3,moved,O
validation,250,4,to,O
validation,250,5,Silicon,B-LOCATION
validation,250,6,Valley,I-LOCATION
validation,250,7,in,O
validation,250,8,tomorrow,B-DATE
validation,250,9,and,O
validation,250,10,started,O
validation,250,11,learning,O
validation,250,12,Hugging,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,250,13,Face,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,250,14,Transformers,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,250,15,.,O
validation,251,1,Sara,B-PERSON
validation,251,2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
validation,251,3,joined,O
validation,251,4,Systems,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,251,5,Limited,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,251,6,in,O
validation,251,7,United,B-LOCATION
validation,251,8,Arab,I-LOCATION
validation,251,9,Emirates,I-LOCATION
validation,251,10,on,O
validation,251,11,September,B-DATE
validation,251,12,2026,I-DATE
validation,251,13,to,O
validation,251,14,work,O
validation,251,15,on,O
validation,251,16,transformer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,251,17,architecture,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,251,18,.,O
validation,252,1,Fatima,B-PERSON
validation,252,2,Noor,I-PERSON
validation,252,3,presented,O
validation,252,4,a,O
validation,252,5,project,O
validation,252,6,on,O
validation,252,7,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,252,8,at,O
validation,252,9,CureMD,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,252,10,during,O
validation,252,11,June,B-DATE
validation,252,12,2026,I-DATE
validation,252,13,.,O
validation,253,1,NetSol,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,253,2,Technologies,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,253,3,announced,O
validation,253,4,a,O
validation,253,5,new,O
validation,253,6,large,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,253,7,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,253,8,models,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,253,9,team,O
validation,253,10,in,O
validation,253,11,Rawalpindi,B-LOCATION
validation,253,12,on,O
validation,253,13,April,B-DATE
validation,253,14,2025,I-DATE
validation,253,15,.,O
validation,254,1,Omar,B-PERSON
validation,254,2,Farooq,I-PERSON
validation,254,3,is,O
validation,254,4,an,O
validation,254,5,engineer,O
validation,254,6,from,O
validation,254,7,United,B-LOCATION
validation,254,8,Arab,I-LOCATION
validation,254,9,Emirates,I-LOCATION
validation,254,10,with,O
validation,254,11,experience,O
validation,254,12,in,O
validation,254,13,computer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,254,14,vision,I-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,254,15,.,O
validation,255,1,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
validation,255,2,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,255,3,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,255,4,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
validation,255,5,is,O
validation,255,6,hiring,O
validation,255,7,graduates,O
validation,255,8,skilled,O
validation,255,9,in,O
validation,255,10,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
validation,255,11,for,O
validation,255,12,its,O
validation,255,13,Saudi,B-LOCATION
validation,255,14,Arabia,I-LOCATION
validation,255,15,office,O
validation,255,16,.,O
test,256,1,Bilal,B-PERSON
test,256,2,Hussain,I-PERSON
test,256,3,will,O
test,256,4,attend,O
test,256,5,an,O
test,256,6,interview,O
test,256,7,at,O
test,256,8,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
test,256,9,on,O
test,256,10,December,B-DATE
test,256,11,2025,I-DATE
test,256,12,.,O
test,257,1,The,O
test,257,2,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,257,3,system,O
test,257,4,was,O
test,257,5,developed,O
test,257,6,by,O
test,257,7,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
test,257,8,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
test,257,9,in,O
test,257,10,Doha,B-LOCATION
test,257,11,.,O
test,258,1,Hamza,B-PERSON
test,258,2,Siddiqui,I-PERSON
test,258,3,used,O
test,258,4,multi,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,258,5,agent,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,258,6,systems,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,258,7,to,O
test,258,8,improve,O
test,258,9,a,O
test,258,10,product,O
test,258,11,built,O
test,258,12,for,O
test,258,13,Pakistani,B-ORGANIZATION
test,258,14,Software,I-ORGANIZATION
test,258,15,Export,I-ORGANIZATION
test,258,16,Board,I-ORGANIZATION
test,258,17,.,O
test,259,1,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
test,259,2,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
test,259,3,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
test,259,4,released,O
test,259,5,its,O
test,259,6,MLOps,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,259,7,research,O
test,259,8,report,O
test,259,9,in,O
test,259,10,March,B-DATE
test,259,11,2026,I-DATE
test,259,12,.,O
test,260,1,Sana,B-PERSON
test,260,2,Javed,I-PERSON
test,260,3,moved,O
test,260,4,to,O
test,260,5,Silicon,B-LOCATION
test,260,6,Valley,I-LOCATION
test,260,7,in,O
test,260,8,5,B-DATE
test,260,9,May,I-DATE
test,260,10,2026,I-DATE
test,260,11,and,O
test,260,12,started,O
test,260,13,learning,O
test,260,14,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,260,15,.,O
test,261,1,Bilal,B-PERSON
test,261,2,Hussain,I-PERSON
test,261,3,joined,O
test,261,4,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
test,261,5,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
test,261,6,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
test,261,7,in,O
test,261,8,Lahore,B-LOCATION
test,261,9,on,O
test,261,10,March,B-DATE
test,261,11,2026,I-DATE
test,261,12,to,O
test,261,13,work,O
test,261,14,on,O
test,261,15,multi,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,261,16,agent,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,261,17,systems,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,261,18,.,O
test,262,1,Maryam,B-PERSON
test,262,2,Tariq,I-PERSON
test,262,3,presented,O
test,262,4,a,O
test,262,5,project,O
test,262,6,on,O
test,262,7,model,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,262,8,fine,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,262,9,tuning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,262,10,at,O
test,262,11,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
test,262,12,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
test,262,13,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
test,262,14,during,O
test,262,15,September,B-DATE
test,262,16,2026,I-DATE
test,262,17,.,O
test,263,1,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
test,263,2,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
test,263,3,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
test,263,4,announced,O
test,263,5,a,O
test,263,6,new,O
test,263,7,LangGraph,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,263,8,team,O
test,263,9,in,O
test,263,10,Islamabad,B-LOCATION
test,263,11,on,O
test,263,12,December,B-DATE
test,263,13,2025,I-DATE
test,263,14,.,O
test,264,1,Nida,B-PERSON
test,264,2,Aslam,I-PERSON
test,264,3,is,O
test,264,4,an,O
test,264,5,engineer,O
test,264,6,from,O
test,264,7,Dubai,B-LOCATION
test,264,8,with,O
test,264,9,experience,O
test,264,10,in,O
test,264,11,MLOps,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,264,12,.,O
test,265,1,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
test,265,2,is,O
test,265,3,hiring,O
test,265,4,graduates,O
test,265,5,skilled,O
test,265,6,in,O
test,265,7,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,265,8,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,265,9,for,O
test,265,10,its,O
test,265,11,Riyadh,B-LOCATION
test,265,12,office,O
test,265,13,.,O
test,266,1,Hamza,B-PERSON
test,266,2,Siddiqui,I-PERSON
test,266,3,will,O
test,266,4,attend,O
test,266,5,an,O
test,266,6,interview,O
test,266,7,at,O
test,266,8,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
test,266,9,University,I-ORGANIZATION
test,266,10,of,I-ORGANIZATION
test,266,11,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
test,266,12,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
test,266,13,on,O
test,266,14,September,B-DATE
test,266,15,2026,I-DATE
test,266,16,.,O
test,267,1,The,O
test,267,2,natural,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,267,3,language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,267,4,processing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,267,5,system,O
test,267,6,was,O
test,267,7,developed,O
test,267,8,by,O
test,267,9,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
test,267,10,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
test,267,11,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
test,267,12,in,O
test,267,13,Johar,B-LOCATION
test,267,14,Town,I-LOCATION
test,267,15,.,O
test,268,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
test,268,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
test,268,3,used,O
test,268,4,FastAPI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,268,5,to,O
test,268,6,improve,O
test,268,7,a,O
test,268,8,product,O
test,268,9,built,O
test,268,10,for,O
test,268,11,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
test,268,12,University,I-ORGANIZATION
test,268,13,of,I-ORGANIZATION
test,268,14,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
test,268,15,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
test,268,16,.,O
test,269,1,Punjab,B-ORGANIZATION
test,269,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
test,269,3,released,O
test,269,4,its,O
test,269,5,feature,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,269,6,engineering,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,269,7,research,O
test,269,8,report,O
test,269,9,in,O
test,269,10,April,B-DATE
test,269,11,2025,I-DATE
test,269,12,.,O
test,270,1,Usman,B-PERSON
test,270,2,Malik,I-PERSON
test,270,3,moved,O
test,270,4,to,O
test,270,5,Lahore,B-LOCATION
test,270,6,in,O
test,270,7,January,B-DATE
test,270,8,2025,I-DATE
test,270,9,and,O
test,270,10,started,O
test,270,11,learning,O
test,270,12,LangChain,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,270,13,.,O
test,271,1,Saad,B-PERSON
test,271,2,Qureshi,I-PERSON
test,271,3,joined,O
test,271,4,Techlogix,B-ORGANIZATION
test,271,5,in,O
test,271,6,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
test,271,7,Lahore,I-LOCATION
test,271,8,on,O
test,271,9,15,B-DATE
test,271,10,July,I-DATE
test,271,11,2026,I-DATE
test,271,12,to,O
test,271,13,work,O
test,271,14,on,O
test,271,15,spaCy,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,271,16,.,O
test,272,1,Sara,B-PERSON
test,272,2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
test,272,3,presented,O
test,272,4,a,O
test,272,5,project,O
test,272,6,on,O
test,272,7,machine,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,272,8,learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,272,9,at,O
test,272,10,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
test,272,11,during,O
test,272,12,December,B-DATE
test,272,13,2025,I-DATE
test,272,14,.,O
test,273,1,Afiniti,B-ORGANIZATION
test,273,2,announced,O
test,273,3,a,O
test,273,4,new,O
test,273,5,computer,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,273,6,vision,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,273,7,team,O
test,273,8,in,O
test,273,9,Gulberg,B-LOCATION
test,273,10,Lahore,I-LOCATION
test,273,11,on,O
test,273,12,today,B-DATE
test,273,13,.,O
test,274,1,Ali,B-PERSON
test,274,2,Raza,I-PERSON
test,274,3,is,O
test,274,4,an,O
test,274,5,engineer,O
test,274,6,from,O
test,274,7,Johar,B-LOCATION
test,274,8,Town,I-LOCATION
test,274,9,with,O
test,274,10,experience,O
test,274,11,in,O
test,274,12,vector,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,274,13,database,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,274,14,.,O
test,275,1,Lahore,B-ORGANIZATION
test,275,2,University,I-ORGANIZATION
test,275,3,of,I-ORGANIZATION
test,275,4,Management,I-ORGANIZATION
test,275,5,Sciences,I-ORGANIZATION
test,275,6,is,O
test,275,7,hiring,O
test,275,8,graduates,O
test,275,9,skilled,O
test,275,10,in,O
test,275,11,named,B-DOMAIN_TERM
test,275,12,entity,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,275,13,recognition,I-DOMAIN_TERM
test,275,14,for,O
test,275,15,its,O
test,275,16,Abu,B-LOCATION
test,275,17,Dhabi,I-LOCATION
test,275,18,office,O
test,275,19,.,O
test,276,1,Ahmed,B-PERSON
test,276,2,Rauf,I-PERSON
test,276,3,will,O
test,276,4,attend,O
test,276,5,an,O
test,276,6,interview,O
test,276,7,at,O
test,276,8,Data,B-ORGANIZATION
test,276,9,Science,I-ORGANIZATION
test,276,10,Lab,I-ORGANIZATION
test,276,11,on,O
