sentence_id,token,label
1,Ali,B-PERSON
1,Khan,I-PERSON
1,works,O
1,at,O
1,Google,B-ORGANIZATION
1,in,O
1,Lahore,B-LOCATION
1,.,O
2,Sarah,B-PERSON
2,Ahmed,I-PERSON
2,joined,O
2,Microsoft,B-ORGANIZATION
2,on,O
2,15,B-DATE
2,March,I-DATE
2,2024,I-DATE
2,.,O
3,Data,B-DOMAIN_TERM
3,Science,I-DOMAIN_TERM
3,teams,O
3,at,O
3,Acme,B-ORGANIZATION
3,Analytics,I-ORGANIZATION
3,expanded,O
3,in,O
3,Karachi,B-LOCATION
3,.,O
4,Fatima,B-PERSON
4,presented,O
4,a,O
4,Natural,B-DOMAIN_TERM
4,Language,I-DOMAIN_TERM
4,Processing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
4,roadmap,O
4,to,O
4,OpenAI,B-ORGANIZATION
4,partners,O
4,.,O
5,The,O
5,Human,B-DOMAIN_TERM
5,Resources,I-DOMAIN_TERM
5,department,O
5,hired,O
5,Omar,B-PERSON
5,in,O
5,New,B-LOCATION
5,York,I-LOCATION
5,City,I-LOCATION
5,.,O
6,IBM,B-ORGANIZATION
6,opened,O
6,an,O
6,AI,B-DOMAIN_TERM
6,Research,I-DOMAIN_TERM
6,Lab,I-DOMAIN_TERM
6,in,O
6,Islamabad,B-LOCATION
6,last,O
6,year,O
6,.,O
7,Ayesha,B-PERSON
7,reviewed,O
7,the,O
7,Machine,B-DOMAIN_TERM
7,Learning,I-DOMAIN_TERM
7,pipeline,O
7,for,O
7,TechNova,B-ORGANIZATION
7,Solutions,I-ORGANIZATION
7,.,O
8,Amazon,B-ORGANIZATION
8,Web,I-ORGANIZATION
8,Services,I-ORGANIZATION
8,trained,O
8,engineers,O
8,in,O
8,Dubai,B-LOCATION
8,during,O
8,June,B-DATE
8,2025,I-DATE
8,.,O
9,Hassan,B-PERSON
9,will,O
9,lead,O
9,the,O
9,Cloud,B-DOMAIN_TERM
9,Computing,I-DOMAIN_TERM
9,initiative,O
9,at,O
9,Nestle,B-ORGANIZATION
9,Pakistan,I-ORGANIZATION
9,.,O
10,The,O
10,team,O
10,met,O
10,Dr.,B-PERSON
10,Nadia,I-PERSON
10,Farooq,I-PERSON
10,at,O
10,Stanford,B-ORGANIZATION
10,University,I-ORGANIZATION
10,on,O
10,Monday,B-DATE
10,.,O
11,Meta,B-ORGANIZATION
11,recruited,O
11,software,O
11,engineers,O
11,from,O
11,San,B-LOCATION
11,Francisco,I-LOCATION
11,for,O
11,Generative,B-DOMAIN_TERM
11,AI,I-DOMAIN_TERM
11,projects,O
11,.,O
12,Zain,B-PERSON
12,completed,O
12,an,O
12,internship,O
12,at,O
12,Siemens,B-ORGANIZATION
12,Healthineers,I-ORGANIZATION
12,in,O
12,Berlin,B-LOCATION
12,in,O
12,2023,B-DATE
12,.,O
13,Oracle,B-ORGANIZATION
13,announced,O
13,a,O
13,Database,B-DOMAIN_TERM
13,Administration,I-DOMAIN_TERM
13,certification,O
13,program,O
13,for,O
13,employees,O
13,.,O
14,Maria,B-PERSON
14,Gomez,I-PERSON
14,managed,O
14,cybersecurity,B-DOMAIN_TERM
14,audits,O
14,for,O
14,HBL,B-ORGANIZATION
14,in,O
14,Saudi,B-LOCATION
14,Arabia,I-LOCATION
14,.,O
15,Tesla,B-ORGANIZATION
15,hired,O
15,Ahmed,B-PERSON
15,Raza,I-PERSON
15,as,O
15,a,O
15,Robotics,B-DOMAIN_TERM
15,Engineer,O
15,on,O
15,1,B-DATE
15,January,I-DATE
15,2026,I-DATE
15,.,O
